(Day 4, morning)
It's a strange question.
(Dormitory for Red)
"Decipher."
"Decipher the code."
What did it say "decipher?"
What are we supposed to decipher?
The lock is locked.
It must be unlocked with a key.
How is that possible?
It's certainly the tulip mania.
We're supposed to decipher something
with this.
What could that be?
After issuing around 400 diamonds today,
it'll be best if White starts a war.
Could someone from Team White
suggest going to war?
It would be hard to bring it up.
- Right. If there are many members,
- Right.
- you have to sound and behave nicely.
- The nice person has a better say.
- Right.
Their deal fell apart.
There will be a few in Team White
that feel annoyed.
Team Blue is away.
Are they talking with another team?
Shall we head out?
You wouldn't answer
no matter how many times we called.
- There was nobody inside.
- We met with them first.
We're pushovers right now.
Look at today's deals.
Based on the first deal of the day,
the pushover is identified.
Those two teams are making a deal.
I believe that we have to show
our presence in this situation.
Then,
the ones who feel mad
can start to have a better say.
- You're right about that.
- The White members...
- aren't fools.
- Right.
They pretend to be good-natured,
but I think they're hiding
an important piece of information.
This is what I think.
Let's say we are to go to war today.
By reason...
By reason,
we have to go against Team Blue.
- Right.
- That's how it is.
We were asked to ally with them
on the first day.
We made a smooth deal with them as well.
They kept their mouths shut
the very next day...
and teamed up with Team Red...
after coming to us first on the first day.
On top of that, we trusted them...
- and paid them in advance.
- We even sold our credits.
- But they dishonored our deal?
- I know.
- If that's the case,
- That's insane if you think about it.
- that's so unprofessional.
- It's making me feel mad.
That's why we have a reason
to strike them first.
- Right.
Anyway, we think it's better for us...
- to ally with Team Blue.
- They're easy to deal with.
Is it solely because
they're easy to deal with...
or is it because
we can get a lot from them?
- We can get a lot from them as well.
- They're easy to deal with...
and we can get a lot from them.
We can also help them
with their skill development.
It's because they aren't a threat to us.
We can't help Team Red
with their skill development.
- They're dealing with a nuclear weapon.
- Right.
It's okay for us to help Team Blue.
The goal of war is to eliminate
our actual threat.
Our actual threat is Team Red.
If they produce a lot of credits,
they can reduce our lives.
They can do that right away.
- Right.
- That's their skill.
Right. So it's right for us
to eliminate our threat.
- That's a strategic approach.
- Right.
That's what war is for.
I thought that we had to strike Team Blue.
The goal of this war is to secure lives.
For us to secure lives,
we must strike Team Blue,
which has the most lives.
But during the morning meeting,
the idea we ended up with
was to ally with Team Blue...
and strike Team Red.
If I didn't feel persuaded by that idea,
I thought about striking Team Blue.
Lives are what we need the most.
If we have a good talk with Team Blue,
the team that has lives,
I thought that war could be avoided today.
I believe that...
war is something that doesn't benefit us.
It should happen only when...
another country tries to invade us.
We can be in a war
from a defensive stance,
but I believe trying to steal
for each other isn't ideal.
I want to head in a direction
in which all of us help each other.
- So that's...
- Right.
I think we're going to
go out after eating.
Day Four has begun.
Team leaders can now be changed.
Discuss whether to
reappoint the current leader.
The supermarket has reopened today.
- Yes!
We can finally eat.
After productive activities are over,
the supermarket can be used...
- starting from lunchtime.
- Right. We can't use it in the morning.
- This concludes the announcement...
- Good thing I had a banana.
from Community Center.
I think it'll be good for us
to talk about our leader situation.
I mentioned yesterday
about the leader holding information...
- and feeling pressure.
- Right.
I said that it would be good for a change
of leaders to prevent those things.
But we learned a lesson from Team Blue.
- A constant leadership change...
- Right.
or a bad takeover will put a team
in so much danger.
- Right.
- We unfortunately witnessed that.
Well,
we've been given certain roles...
- and have adjusted to them.
- Right.
If we force ourselves with a change,
the other team at the negotiation table
will also be confused.
It will confuse us as well, to be honest.
- But it will bring this effect.
- That will be the flow.
- If we change our leader today,
- Right.
the other teams will feel
a greater threat of war.
- It will be easier to be with Team Blue.
- Why?
- I also think...
- Do you think I'll start a war?
- a change is needed.
- Right. That's your image.
- That's why I think...
- Right.
- there's no need for a change today.
When she made negotiations
with the other team,
she calmly persuaded them step by step.
If I were a Team Blue member,
I wouldn't have traded with our team.
- But she got them to sit with us.
- Right.
- And...
- That's Luna's strength.
- Right. That's her strength.
- Right.
I said this next to her on purpose.
"We can go to war,"
"and you can become our target."
- She was 7, and I was 3 to them.
- Right.
She became the good cop,
and I became the bad cop.
- And the pacifist joined in.
- Right.
After creating this situation,
- if I suddenly show up as a leader...
- Then, they will all get ready.
- "They're preparing for war."
- Right.
I'm a pacifist as well!
- Anyway, that ended up becoming my image.
- Right.
The leadership change might be seen...
- as a signal.
- Right.
- So Leia...
should use this as leverage.
"If this carries on,"
"the hardliners of our team
will gain more power."
And naturally,
- I'm a good person!
- we can use this as an advantage.
- We've gained another weapon.
- Right.
So we'll carry on with our leader.
- We can stay if we do that.
- Right.
For the benefit of our team,
- the one who leads our team...
- Right.
is quite important.
We should discuss
who should be our leader.
Right now...
Do you want to be the leader? Or...
I do want to be the leader.
I've tried talking
with the others yesterday.
There's a certain right...
- that a leader has.
- Actually,
when considering the role of a leader,
the main focus is making negotiations
with the other teams.
Up until now,
I've done all of the negotiating...
and uncomfortable talks
with the other teams.
I was wondering if I could...
continue to take that role...
and represent our team.
Right.
Pitou naturally showed her desire...
of wanting to become the leader
since yesterday.
But to be honest,
I feel quite anxious about Pitou.
It felt like she kept trying to
threaten my position.
"I should stop her from becoming
the leader."
This was the thought I got.
That was why I went with,
"I want to be the leader."
I thought that Genie
shouldn't be our leader.
Ultimately,
the fact that the leader
could affect our lives...
wasn't shared with us on the first day.
I felt a chill down my spine.
I thought,
"The leader could get us killed."
She was someone I felt anxious about,
and I had to let her handle
this mission...
of having to submit our lives...
every single day.
I decided that it would be better
for me to become the leader.
This is why I thought it would be better
for me to take this role.
I think it's hard to find the midpoint...
- for the three of us.
- Right.
You are someone who seeks peace.
You are a hardliner.
I'm sure the others know this as well.
I'm the one who mediates.
I believe that...
I'm the most neutral...
- out of the three of us.
- I thought that...
you were the one with a driving force...
and sought war.
And she was the one who sought peace.
I thought that
I was the one in the middle.
As the one in the middle,
I believed that my role...
was to fight for our team.
I think that both of you...
are total hardliners.
None of you are in the middle.
The leader's main role
is to conduct negotiations.
During those negotiations,
I was the one who represented our team.
Isn't that the leader?
Is the one in the back the leader?
I didn't step up because I was incapable.
I was capable,
but I trusted our leader to do a good job.
Our leader is smart and competent. So...
Right. I thought that the one capable...
should be the leader.
There's a benefit to being young.
I sensed that the other leaders
understood me better...
since I was young.
I'm never trying to force everyone
to make me the leader until the end.
- And...
- As we go through each day,
this discussion will continue to pile up.
I believe it's right to make a change now
if we are to make a change.
When considering our relationship
with the others,
I believe it's right for someone
who is less strong to be the leader.
You're definitely not someone
who is less strong.
I don't think we'll reach an agreement
based on who is stronger.
Well...
It doesn't matter if we go through a vote.
Well, it's just the three of us.
That just means
it's based on Salt's decision.
After going through a vote,
I'm fine with reaching a decision
for the best of our team.
Salt said this to me.
She said that she's someone...
who struggles to talk about
uncomfortable topics.
She said that she felt impressed
and grateful...
when I stood up for her
during those situations.
I started a campaign...
to get one person's vote.
As of right now,
I have a greater trust in myself...
more than Genie.
This is based on the better of our team.
Salt and I both have the same opinion...
of being against having
a strong person as a leader.
You might've figured it out,
but I'm a value-oriented person.
I watched the two of you...
when we made deals.
You two always asked for
a greater price...
than what I thought.
More than what I consider to be enough,
you two need a lot more...
- to consider it to be enough.
- Right.
We're completely different in that sense.
At this level,
Pitou is closer to what I think.
Genie feels a bit more distant...
in terms of that.
So...
I do believe Pitou could be
a better leader for us.
Before this,
I had a conversation with Pitou.
Let's say we lose the war...
and lose half of what we have.
Will you consider ditching Genie...
and surviving with just the two of us?
If there's a way,
it would be the best
to make everyone survive.
But if that is to happen,
she can't be...
the leader.
We know what Genie was like
during Season One.
I was surprised on the second day...
by something that wasn't shared with me
on the first day.
It's best to prevent those dangers
if possible.
That was why Pitou became the leader.
As of right now,
I believe that could be
a good decision for us.
Okay. I will follow that decision.
Your opinion matters to me
in this situation.
Team leaders can now be changed
at the Community Center.
Okay! Let's go!
Let's get going.
(Vector enters the Community Center
as soon as it opens.)
I'm here to answer the question.
Please submit your answer sheet
to the central box.
The answer is being checked.
Please wait for a moment.
This should be the order
of how our answers are submitted.
We'll go with the worst answer first.
We'll submit the next best answer
after that.
We'll develop our skill anyway.
- Right.
- That's how we should prepare ourselves.
Skill development for Team White
is now over.
- What?
- Team White...
can no longer submit
skill development answers.
Team White can no longer submit
The answer has been submitted.
Please collect Team White's skill card...
from the central box.
The skill card cannot be used
by Team Black.
Please use the card after purchasing it...
- from the supermarket.
- The supermarket?
- Black got the answer.
Black got the answer.
Gosh!
We should've gotten the answer first!
Black did it.
Does that mean Black got the answer?
- Good job.
- Nice.
Black finally did it.
- I think Black got it right.
- Black got it right!
Black got it right!
- I got goosebumps.
- Gosh!
I got goosebumps!
- I got goosebumps!
- Look!
I got goosebumps!
Skill development for Team Blue
is now over.
He must've gotten all of our answers!
Team Blue can no longer submit
skill development answers.
Skill development for Team Blue
is now over.
- He got all of the answers.
- It's Black. This is crazy.
He got all of the answers.
Team Blue can no longer submit
skill development answers.
Black got the hang of it.
Don't tell me he got Team Red's answer.
He might've gotten Team Red's answer.
I'm curious.
Let's ask.
- He got Team Red's answer as well.
Skill development for Team Red
is now over.
What?
Team Red can no longer submit
skill development answers.
- It worked out for us. We're stuck here.
- Right.
Please use the card after purchasing it
from the supermarket.
We won't be using it.
Right.
(Black obtained all skill cards.)
(Team White's skill card:
Digital Currency Issuance Authority)
(When Team White possesses this card,)
(diamonds can be issued
without any limit.)
(Team Blue's skill card:
Right to Access Information)
(The team that possesses this card
can use 1 life each day...)
(to check a certain team's quantity
of 1 resource and the value of diamonds.)
Three lives will be destroyed immediately.
(Team Red's skill card:
Bomb Manufacturing License)
(The team that possesses this card
can spend 10 credits to make 1 bomb.)
This is amazing.
(Bomb: Destroys 3 lives immediately
of the designated team)
Skill development for all teams
is now over.
(When this sentence gets completed,)
(the total life supply...)
(will reduce by ten.)
The completed sentence...
has been applied to Community Town.
(Total life supply: 34)
(Total life supply: 24)
Let's see how it affects us.
- The sentence has been completed.
- Black's supermarket...
will turn into the Platform.
See? It has changed.
From now on, all teams can make trades
only through the Platform.
The Platform will open
after today's productive activities.
Please check the rule card
for more details.
(Cheering)
Platform!
After coming to the Community Town,
this was the most thrilling moment.
I've been through...
all kinds of suppression, slander,
and misunderstanding.
A chance for me to take revenge has come.
(Vector, Businessman)
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)
(5. We Will All Die in the End)
(Vector has come to check
the response of the residents.)
We have to be prepared in advance.
So what gets applied?
That has to be shared.
- We have to meet Black for that.
It has already been applied, right?
- It has been applied.
- But we're not aware of it.
- Right. That's what's scary about it.
- Right.
Can we head to Black right away?
- We can just run out to meet him.
- Should we run out and catch him?
- Let's go.
- Should we run down?
- Just a few of us should go.
- Right.
Darn it. This is so annoying.
Just the two of you should go.
We'll wait here.
- We'll wait here.
- Okay.
(Paul and Luna head out to meet Vector.)
Can we head out right now?
We might be able to
during the leader appointment.
We have 30 minutes.
I want to head out...
- and ask Black.
- Right.
- Head out.
- Would you like to head out?
- I'll go and look for him.
- Right.
Hold on.
Donkey is coming to see me?
(Sighing)
Darn it.
We should've just gone for the answer.
But I don't think we had the right answer.
- There's Vector!
- There he is.
I can't believe him.
Check out that madness.
- My goodness, sir.
- Sir.
You've gone through a lot of trouble.
What was the answer?
- You've done a lot today.
- Tell us the answer.
I'm not quite sure.
- Hello.
- Sir.
Why did you answer so many questions?
I spent all night on them.
Really?
Will you tell us the answer?
Well,
I'll think about it.
I should share the information I have...
starting from now.
I'll tell you this.
It's a big win for Team White.
If they hear that,
won't Team Red feel anxious...
- and find us to be a threat?
- No.
There's news for Team Red as well.
- I'll tell them separately.
- Right.
With skill development,
- damage comes in the end.
- Right.
It's up to us to use those skills...
- for the good of everyone.
- Right.
Or things can get ruined...
if we wish to use them
for just for our own team's benefit.
Fortunately, we're good people.
- That's what's fortunate.
- What's fortunate...
is that I blocked Team White's skill.
(Understanding)
- But...
- So...
you can choose not to sell it to us.
I will never sell Team White's skill.
- I see.
- He can choose not to sell it.
It's because that will
cut down my prize money.
Can't we give you that much more?
No.
I can't trust that offer.
But if you decide not to sell it
to Team White...
- and sell it to Team Red or Team Blue...
- No.
I've been saying this constantly.
I'm neutral.
- I won't sell it to all teams.
- I was wondering.
I'll open it to everyone
if I'm willing to sell it.
- Right.
- Well,
we have no intention of buying it at all.
- We won't be using it.
- Exactly.
I've checked the skill.
It's hard to use.
Even if we have a skill,
- we have no intention of...
- I'm sure your team will use it.
I'm pretty sure.
- I know what it is.
- Why is she laughing?
- He got us.
- I know what it is.
- No. I'm sure your team will use it.
- No.
Good luck with your productive activities.
- Good luck!
Gosh.
He can't say that.
Say what?
- Say what?
- He basically revealed that...
- we issued a lot of diamonds yesterday.
- Right.
He said that in front
of a Team Red member.
- Fortunately, it wasn't Maillard.
- Right.
I'm not sure how Donkey
will share about this.
(Sighing)
This is so annoying.
- Were you able to get something?
- He didn't tell us.
- He didn't tell you, right?
He didn't tell you?
There's a good chance...
we can't issue diamonds without limit now.
- That's right.
- Probably.
Team Black stole that power from us.
Up to a maximum of 200,
we'll have to lower the percentage...
- from here on out.
- Right.
Team Black has too much power now.
I don't know...
if him staying neutral
is actually neutral...
- for the rest. I mean...
- From now on?
Helping the underdog,
even though power shifts constantly?
- Neutral means a balance of power.
- I mean,
it's up to the individual's judgment now,
and that comes with a lot of errors.
In the end, that'll lead to an imbalance.
- I won all the skills.
- Okay.
- The effect?
- Nicely done.
Life reserves decrease by ten.
- They decrease?
- Yes.
Fortunately,
- the Platform will open starting today.
- Okay.
I'll give Team Red some lives
at a low price.
- Why? To keep you alive, Donkey.
- Thanks.
- Also...
- Second,
I came up with a fake code.
Please let me know if people...
- start doubting or talking.
- Got it.
I'll come up with a new one.
Right, got it.
- Sure.
- You get what I said, right?
(Vector and Donkey share
the fake wall code.)
It's taking him a while.
I'm stepping out as well.
Sure.
They're not even bothering to vote
for my reelection as leader now.
They couldn't even care.
(Team Red's Maillard, reelected as leader)
Letting the others solve it themselves...
I think that'd be better.
- This could be bad...
- Right.
or good. So...
Congratulations, Vector.
- It was no joke.
- Izaha...
Did you need something?
No, I just got curious.
You were taking a while.
- Team White was here earlier.
- I see.
Here's something I only wanted...
- to tell Team Red.
- Sure.
I want an alliance,
and with Team Red if possible.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why? Because you think
we have what it takes?
To be honest, yes.
- We've been doing our best.
- Honestly,
you guys were the most help
with cracking the code.
- Right.
- Nice.
- That's why,
- Yes?
when the Platform comes online,
I might be able to store some resources.
If you need it, unlike the other teams,
we can strike a deal at a fair price.
- But I want your word in exchange.
- Sure.
Yesterday, Maillard...
worked the crowd
and threw shade at me a little.
- I struggled with that.
- It hurt you a lot.
(The previous morning)
He won't give us the code.
Why aren't you giving us the code?
I can't because I don't have it.
- I really don't have it.
- Oh, please.
I heard that Team Black has the code.
Yes, I heard that too.
No, it said I could know the code or not.
- Your word keeps changing.
- The lies continue.
- There's a hint of that.
- I agree.
- But...
- How can I trust him?
I wasn't able to check.
I seriously don't have it.
Can't we challenge Team Black to a war?
Are you kidding me?
I'd appreciate your trust and assistance.
Up until now,
you were just a small shop owner.
But now, you own a huge market.
- I've come into a little power.
- Your influence has grown.
- It's like you own Coupang now.
- Yes, Coupang should do it.
I worked hard to crack it
to stop Team White...
- from obtaining its skill.
- Theirs is too strong.
We don't know all the skills, but still.
Honestly, it'll be like
being robbed blind...
- in broad daylight.
- That's right.
- What if they issued 100 million of them?
- Exactly.
Our diamonds would be worth...
- less than a cent a piece.
- I know.
It'll become the key currency.
They'll become the US.
I had to stop at least that.
- It was in the public interest.
- That's true.
I think Team Black's power...
is needed to maintain balance here.
Right.
I have mixed feelings
regarding Team Black.
But I'm one of the people who trusts him.
I feel like he treats Team Red well...
and has been upfront
about wanting an alliance.
Even though he's a bit suspicious,
I think he's someone
we can somewhat trust.
Vector and I have been signaling...
that we want an alliance
between our teams.
He's been reasonable with our team so far,
like he's being considerate.
I think the Platform...
will pose as a neutral ground for balance,
but it won't actually allow
easy resource exchanges...
and will let specific teams gain
an unfair advantage.
It is going to act
as the true invisible hand.
We're at a disadvantage.
We talked to Vector.
What's the correct answer?
He hasn't told us yet.
- Really?
- That's right.
He did say it might not be good for us.
As in the effect.
According to him,
Red is at a disadvantage with the skills.
Since he wants to keep things balanced,
he wants to show us his good faith.
Why would he want balance?
Apparently, his goal is...
to make everyone live well together.
Judging by his words and actions,
I think he's telling the truth.
- Does he need as many people alive?
- Right, so...
He was especially hurt by what you said.
- While everyone was around, you...
- What?
He's the one who lied.
So please don't upset him...
- Don't seek pity.
- when everyone's around.
Team Black gained a lot of power
by cracking every riddle.
If we cooperate,
he'll do his best to help us
to our advantage.
That's what Black said.
I think we should play nice with him
for a while...
and utilize that.
I couldn't stand it.
Everything's going to go
the way Black wants now.
The situation is worse.
Hey, there's something there.
Those are the rules on
how the Platform operates.
The Platform operation rules.
"When all the skills are developed..."
"Team Black's skill will be activated,
which is the transition to the Platform."
When all the skills are developed,
Team Black's skill will be activated,
which is the transition to the Platform.
Once the Platform is activated,
the existing Trading Station
will be closed.
From now on, all transactions
will be handled through the Platform.
They're closing the Trading Station?
We can't trade by ourselves anymore.
The teams can't trade now, right?
The trade we used to do...
with other teams
must now only be conducted...
under Black's watch.
- Before,
- We'll be at a disadvantage...
he was only told the trading results.
Now he can interfere...
- with the trades directly?
- Yes, he can interfere.
"At the Platform, direct bartering..."
"like trading lives and credits
isn't possible anymore."
(Bartering is prohibited.)
"Only diamonds are accepted as currency."
(Only diamonds are accepted as currency.)
"Credits aren't accepted as currency
on the Platform."
- In other words, we have a currency now.
- Right.
Before, it was the primitive ages.
Now, we've entered the age of currency.
- Exactly. You're right.
- Right.
From here on out,
you can't buy or sell without diamonds.
That's right, which is good for us.
- We're at an advantage.
- Right.
On top of that,
- credits are no longer needed to trade.
- That's right.
If credits can't be used to trade,
then the credits...
- Is it worth nothing now?
- We can't buy lives with it.
We'll have to buy them with diamonds
at the Platform.
We can no longer buy lives with credits.
We're worthless now.
Absolutely worthless.
"You may operate the Platform..."
"even without receiving lives
from other teams."
Are lives no longer used at all?
It's a transition,
rather than an addition.
That's what I got so far.
Are you kidding me?
- Let's go.
- What do we do with our credits now?
But why...
What do you gain
by monopolizing the Platform?
Whoever operates it
might receive a commission.
We could pay 50 diamonds,
only to get 45 of something back...
because of a commission.
Black's revenue stream shifted
from only direct sales...
to earning business commissions too.
- Black's gaining power.
- There will be a commission.
Now that the Platform is open,
Black could make an earning
through commissions.
- He's in "show me the money" mode.
- He has power.
He has all the power.
- Tell me about it.
- He'll have a different attitude today.
He's been acting like that
since yesterday.
The Platform that has all three skills...
is operational?
He's going to rake in money.
Shortly, today's productive activity
will begin.
The keyword
for today's productive activity...
is Fermi estimation.
What's Fermi estimation again?
- We learned it in season 1.
- It came up in season 1.
Why don't I remember it?
I didn't take part in that round.
Darn, this is a tough one.
- This isn't my expertise.
- I'm clueless.
I don't know anything about it.
Shall we get going?
Team Blue won't be able to produce
a lot of lives today.
This is bad.
They could be better at this
than we think. I believe in them.
If a war breaks out today,
- Exactly.
- we'll be in trouble too.
We need to go back
to living harmoniously together.
We need to shift our stance.
- Here we go.
- Bring the fire.
(All three teams arrive
at the production site.)
Team Blue will be made aware...
of the life reserves
before the productive activity begins.
There are 24 lives currently...
- What?
- in reserve.
- Wait. Hold on.
- What did we just hear?
That doesn't make any sense.
There were 43,
and we dug up five yesterday.
We estimated that each
of the other teams got two.
Yes, but even so...
- I mean...
- Wait, only 24?
It should be 34. There's 10 missing.
- Ten of them?
- Black must've taken them.
They must've gone to Black.
It was a huge slap in the face.
Ten of the lives suddenly went missing.
We were short on lives as it was,
and I was suddenly lost for words.
It's just crazy.
(Salt, Writer)
Where did they go?
It had to be Black.
This morning, it was announced
that he cracked...
the riddles for the skills.
The Platform suddenly became operational,
and now ten lives are missing
from the reserves.
What was the skill that was developed?
What was it that triggered all of this?
- He cracked Team Blue's riddle too.
- Exactly.
Is that what caused the drop in lives?
- Is this what took effect?
- Lives weren't added.
They decreased.
No way.
We might have to buy lives from Black now.
- Rather than...
- You're right.
That makes the most sense.
Whoever it is,
someone gaining more power...
means the collapse
of the market system in some way.
I felt like he came in
to some massive power.
The situation keeps changing.
So rather than sticking
to a specific strategy,
we don't know
how quickly things might change,
so for now, we should focus
on collecting lives.
We'll go with the lives.
We'll produce lives.
Lives.
We'll go with credits.
Today's production keyword
is "Fermi estimation."
Fermi estimation.
(Today's production activity:
Fermi estimation)
Fermi estimation is a game...
in which you estimate
an approximate answer to a problem...
using only basic knowledge
and logical reasoning.
For each question,
players have one opportunity...
to spend one credit to request a hint.
Only answers
within the specified margin of error...
for each question
will be accepted as correct.
In Fermi estimation only,
if an answer is incorrect,
it will be revealed
whether the correct answer...
is higher or lower
than the submitted answer.
Hold on. So is it better to try again,
or should we use a hint?
- That's...
- Telling us whether...
it's higher or lower is also a hint.
If you have enough credits,
you can definitely get the answer.
- That's right.
- In the Fermi estimation game,
you can always get the answer right
if you have enough credits.
- All teams are low on credits, right?
- Right.
- We haven't been producing them.
- Yes.
(Current amount of credits:
Red 5, White 5, Blue 6)
- That's modest.
- Yes. Our...
I thought we were a bit doomed.
Since Fermi estimation
has a defined range,
making more attempts
gives you a fairly high chance...
of getting the correct answer.
If you have enough credits,
you could afford to make ten attempts.
Starting with only five
was pretty disappointing.
Please insert one credit
into the credit box.
Here's the first question.
Based on Korean statistics
from April 2025,
what was the average amount
an adult spent...
on food delivery apps in a month?
First of all, whenever you order something
through a delivery app,
it usually costs
at least 20 to 30 dollars.
- There's the minimum order amount...
- The minimum order amount.
- and the delivery fee.
- That's right.
We could go with 20 dollars.
I think it would come out
to around 300 to 400 dollars.
Do people order so much?
People really order
a lot of delivery food.
I see.
People these days think
delivery food is more efficient...
because they order once...
- and eat that over many meals.
- That's right.
You eat portions of it.
People order food a lot.
For a 20-dollar order
to amount to 300 dollars,
- they'd have to order fifteen times.
- Fifteen times.
An average adult
orders delivery about 15 times a month?
Fifteen times?
Half the month?
We could share how much we each spend.
I'm a one-person household,
and I spend around 40 dollars.
That's the amount you spend
on delivery apps in a month?
- You had a higher amount, right?
- Right.
Do you not use the delivery app so often?
I don't use it so much. I normally cook...
- my meals.
- I also don't use it so much.
There's coffee as well.
You shouldn't think about the meals only.
How much do you spend
on delivery apps, Paul?
I think it's below 300 dollars.
I think I spend around 200 dollars.
- Really?
- Yes.
I normally cook at home,
but I also order in a lot.
I think I spend around 800 to 900 dollars.
But you eat with your wife.
- That's just me.
- You alone?
If I order 1 dish,
it's around 10 to 15 dollars.
When I order 2 dishes,
that would be 20 to 30 dollars.
How many times a week
do you order delivery?
Well...
About 5 to 10 times.
- A week?
- Yes.
- It's because...
Ten times? Do you order two times a day?
That's right.
- I sometimes order...
- That's...
lunch and dinner.
I order delivery for lunch and dinner.
For example, I eat rice bowls
or pork cutlets for lunch,
then order tteokbokki for dinner.
I sometimes order jokbal or bossam,
and chicken, more often.
I don't think I eat that much.
You do eat a lot.
No. I'm an average person.
What are you talking about?
What kind of person...
orders delivery for both lunch and dinner?
A lot of people do that these days.
- Really?
- There are many people.
There's a big difference.
Since it's an average amount,
we have to consider those...
- who don't order delivery.
- That's right.
We could lower that estimate a bit.
For one family,
three hundred dollars a month
on delivery apps...
is a pretty big expense.
- Then 250 dollars?
- Shall we go with 250 dollars?
- Or two hundred forty?
- Two hundred forty.
What's our average income?
It's around 3,000 dollars,
and the median income is lower than that.
So, if we use 3,000 dollars
as the baseline,
how much do we spend on food each month?
Isn't it usually around 15 percent?
- How much is that? It's 450 dollars.
- It's 450 dollars.
We eat three meals a day.
Three times seven is twenty-one.
We eat 11 times a week,
but we order delivery
only 2 or 3 times a week.
So that would mean
spending 2 or 3 out of 21...
of the total food budget on delivery.
- If we think about it.
- That would be 150 dollars.
- On delivery costs.
- Let's try 150 dollars.
Should we try 160 dollars?
Even if we estimate it at 160 dollars,
we can still cover the 150-dollar range
with a 10 percent margin of error, right?
What about 150 dollars?
I don't think
the delivery market is small.
- What about 145 dollars?
- Let's go with 145 dollars.
We also have to check out
the other questions.
- We can't stay stuck here.
- Right.
- Let's go with 145 dollars.
The answer is 145 dollars.
The answer is 160 dollars.
- Two hundred forty dollars.
- Okay.
The margin of error is ten percent.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is lower than your submitted answer.
Goodness.
It's lower than 144 dollars.
It's way lower.
- See? It's lower.
- It's lower.
- It's lower. Two hundred forty is high.
- But this is rather...
- I'm sorry.
- Right.
I'll stay quiet today.
Should we try again?
Hold on.
So...
It's quite tough.
- According to my calculations...
- Three hundred.
I don't remember the exact figure,
but Baemin's annual revenue...
is roughly four billion dollars.
Baemin's revenue comes from commissions
based on the total payment amount.
- Fifteen percent.
- It's higher.
As far as I know,
it's more than 20 percent.
If we assume they take
a 20 percent commission,
the total payment amount
would be around 20 billion dollars.
There's Naver...
- Coupang Eats.
- and Coupang Eats as well.
So if we assume it takes half the orders,
the total annual transaction volume
through food delivery apps...
is around 40 billion dollars.
If we assume a population of 40 million,
that comes out to 1,000 dollars
per person per year.
If the annual spending per person
is 1,000 dollars,
that's about 83 dollars per month.
So it's way lower than we thought.
We're also including
the elderly population.
- Right. The elderly...
- They spend less.
- It's lower than we thought.
- may order delivery once a month.
There must be
a lot of elderly users as well.
Yes.
After hearing
that it was a Fermi estimation game,
I took my calculator from the dormitory.
I took out my calculator
and started calculating the likely ranges.
And based
on the background knowledge I had,
I think I set some initial guidelines
to start with.
At 118 dollars,
we can cover a range
from 106 to 130 dollars.
We could say 118 dollars...
or 97 dollars.
We could say 97 dollars,
and if it's higher,
- we can answer it the next time.
- It would be 118 dollars.
- Should we narrow it down like that?
- So 97 dollars?
It's not perfect, but let's go with that.
We'll try again.
Please insert one credit
into the credit box.
The answer is 97 dollars.
(Team Red's submitted answer: 97 dollars)
Is it higher or lower?
That is correct.
- That was on point.
- Yes!
- Stop eating so much!
- Right.
- The delivery app market...
- I'll stop eating.
Forty billion dollars was enough.
You got it exactly right.
We spent 1 credit and earned 3 credits.
- It's not bad.
- Right.
That's a bummer.
- Pass.
We'll move on to the next question.
- Let's go.
- Give us the next question.
Here's the next question.
(As of the 2nd half of 2025,
the average cost of a standard room...)
(at postpartum care centers nationwide
for 14 days is 3,730 dollars.)
(What is the average cost
of a 14-day stay in a premium suite...)
(at a postpartum care center
in Gangnam-gu, Seoul?)
Gangnam-gu.
It's a premium suite. That would cost
tens of thousands of dollars.
It would be more than 10,000 dollars.
It's really expensive.
- This...
- It's around 10,000 dollars.
I got chills after hearing the price.
It's more than 10,000 dollars.
It's about 10,000 dollars.
I once did a feature...
- on a postpartum care center in Gangnam.
- Really?
It's definitely more than 10,000 dollars.
What do they offer
at a postpartum care center? Food...
- Massages.
- They teach you about the baby.
Their services are totally different.
It must be more than 1,000 a day then.
It's Gangnam-gu in the first place.
The land prices...
They'd have to charge a high price there.
- It's a premium suite too.
- Otherwise, it's hard to estimate.
- Even accommodations...
- Even just staying at a hotel...
It costs 1,000 dollars a day...
to stay at the Shilla Hotel.
If we say it's 14,000 dollars,
that's still 1,000 dollars a day.
I think people there
would spend 1,000 dollars easily.
If it's the average price
for the premium suites...
- Let's say 15,000 dollars.
- So, 15,000 dollars?
- It's 15,000 dollars.
- It's probably higher than that.
It's definitely higher.
If we say it's 18,000 dollars,
it's 1,330 dollars a day.
Wouldn't it be that much?
- It should be around 18,000 dollars.
- It's really expensive.
I've seen places
that cost 30,000 dollars for 2 weeks.
Places like that are booked up
a year in advance.
Since 20,000 dollars covers
18,000 dollars,
shall we go with 20,000 dollars?
Let's go with 20,000 dollars.
Since 10 percent of 20,000 dollars
is 2,000 dollars,
it can cover a wide range.
I think 20,000 dollars is a good estimate.
Okay.
Twenty thousand.
Dollars.
- Twenty thousand.
- Dollars.
- "Dollars."
- Suddenly.
- Twenty thousand dollars.
- Not two thousand dollars.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer...
- is lower than your submitted answer.
- It's lower?
It's lower than that?
- We set it too high.
- It was too high.
The answer is 14,000 dollars.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is higher than your submitted answer.
- That makes it harder.
- Should we pass this one?
In today's questions,
- there is no limit to how high it is.
- Right.
Trying again isn't...
- Shall we move on?
- It's hard to narrow it down.
That's right.
We'll pass.
Here's the correct answer.
(Answer: 16,670 dollars
Margin of error: 15,000 to 18,340 dollars)
One slot.
We could have gotten it right
if we had said 15,000 dollars.
We should have raised it by 1,000 dollars.
- We just needed one more slot.
- We should have put 1,000 dollars more.
We were so close.
It was 17,000 dollars.
- We could have said 18,000 dollars.
- If we had said 18,000 dollars,
- we would've gotten it right.
- Boss has a great instinct today.
- Am I on fire today?
- Let's go.
- We...
- We have a great instinct.
Let's trust our gut feeling.
- Okay.
- We just don't have enough evidence.
I have a feeling...
- Team Blue will bring only one life.
- Right.
It wouldn't be easy.
Fifteen thousand dollars?
- Fifteen thousand dollars?
Or 14,500 dollars?
- So, 14,500 dollars?
Okay. Let's try again. I don't think...
people will do well
in this Fermi estimation.
(What is the average cost
of a 14-day stay in a premium suite...)
(at a postpartum care center
in Gangnam-gu, Seoul?)
- Shall we go with 14,500 dollars?
- Let's go.
Okay. It's 14,500 dollars.
- Fourteen thousand five hundred dollars.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is higher than your submitted answer.
What? Hold on.
- It's higher than 14,500 dollars.
- If it's higher...
- We're pretty close.
- Right.
- We said 20,000 earlier, right?
- We said 20,000 dollars.
So it's lower than 18,000 dollars.
We were so close.
- We were so close.
- We'd get lives...
- if we try again.
- It's higher than 15,950 dollars...
and lower than 18,000 dollars.
- Would 16,800 dollars do?
- So 16,800 dollars.
That covers 18,480 dollars too.
- Lower than 18,000 dollars.
- Yes.
- They both work.
- It certainly fits.
Good. Let's go with that.
- Please.
This is crazy.
We'll try again.
The answer is 16,800 dollars.
That is correct.
We would have gotten it right
if we had gone with 15,000 dollars!
- That's right.
- I said 15,000 dollars.
- Forget it. Let's move on.
- Right.
We got it anyway.
- We got it right.
- Right.
We did well.
- Here's the next question.
- Senior welfare facilities...
- It's definitely lower than that.
- Right.
As of 2024.
- There were 96,430 facilities.
- There were...
How many childcare centers were there?
As far as I know, there are...
- around 2,000 elementary schools.
- Around 2,000?
There are more
prostitution establishments than that.
When there are 96,000
senior welfare facilities?
There are so many seniors.
This is a relatively easy question.
Should we calculate this by generation?
These days, there are about 200,000 people
in each generation.
In each year of age.
So there are about 1.2 million children...
aged 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
- Children?
- Yes.
The number of newborns
has fallen below 300,000.
- I think it was in the 200,000 range.
- Around 200,000?
Each childcare center...
They have fewer than 30 children.
Then around 33,000 centers?
I think it's a really small number.
I think it would be fewer.
You had a great gut feeling.
What was your estimate?
I feel like it's around 4,000.
Just double the number
of elementary schools.
- That's just a feeling.
- Your feeling might be on point.
- It's just a feeling.
- We could go with Boss' feeling.
Four thousand?
I'll take responsibility.
The guilt. Four thousand.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is higher than your submitted answer.
- We'll go with our feeling.
- I think it's 6,000.
When you calculate it,
if the population...
is 1.2 million,
and 60 percent goes to a childcare center,
then that's 720,000 children.
If one center has a capacity
of around 20 children,
that makes it 36,000.
- Thirty-six thousand?
- Yes.
That's too many.
There was only one option
in my neighborhood.
It could be ridiculously low.
Having raised kids,
the number seems ridiculously low.
Seventeen thousand?
If we say 17,777,
it roughly makes it.
It's not a great number, though.
But it's quite tough
to find childcare centers.
- Seventeen thousand seven hundred?
Let's go with that.
Seventeen thousand seven hundred.
- That is incorrect.
- It's higher.
The correct answer
is higher than your submitted answer.
It's higher.
Seventeen thousand seven hundred.
If you wish to retry,
ring the bell to make your request.
Should we try again?
We could skip the next section.
Shall we go with 28,900?
We went with 17,000.
If we get it wrong,
we can do it again
and go with the section below.
- Let's try that.
- Let's go with 28,900.
We'll try again.
The answer is 28,900.
That is correct.
- That's amazing.
- That was brilliant.
- Nice.
- That was amazing.
You're amazing.
That was amazing.
He analyzed the sections as well.
I felt so reassured.
Izaha brought his calculator right away.
He's really good at solving problems.
How did you make an estimate
from those numbers?
I really think the other teams
are in trouble today.
Here's the next question.
(The total attendance
for the KBO regular season was 328,318.)
(How many attendees were there in 2025?)
(Margin of error: 10 percent)
I know nothing about baseball.
I have no idea either.
- Baseball? I don't know.
- I don't watch baseball.
Are there no baseball fans here?
In 2024...
- Calculate it like this.
- I do that as well.
- One, two, three, four.
- Couldn't you do this?
Should I try that? Should I go there?
- Yes.
- I'll go since I'm an idiot.
Idiots are good at such things.
Since we're idiots...
Idiots are good at it.
Come and measure it.
Wait.
- Nice.
- Don't laugh.
- But that's the best.
- I feel embarrassed.
- That's the length of one pen.
- It would be similar.
One pen cap. Let me see.
- One.
I look so dumb.
- Four.
It's just the feeling. Five.
Six.
One, two.
Compared to 2021, 2022...
As of 2020...
Judging by eye,
it's around 23 times as much.
We have to multiply it.
It's been so long
since I've done multiplication.
Seven times two is fourteen.
Twenty-two.
What is that?
Seven million?
I got 7,117,600.
But I have heard a lot
about how many people go to the games.
I think it could be more.
- Me too.
- I think it's around ten million people.
- I think I heard that it was ten million.
- I think I read somewhere...
that there were more
than ten million people.
- Total attendance.
- You know, that graph...
- They would have drawn a reasonable one.
- These days, Excel...
probably adjusts...
- the proportions automatically.
- Yes.
Shall we trust that graph?
That's a good idea.
Let's go with 7.1 million.
- Shall we go with 7.1 million?
- Let's go with that.
The answer is 7.1 million.
The answer is 7,550,304.
That is incorrect.
- The correct answer...
- It's higher.
is higher than your submitted answer.
- Draw the graph properly.
- I know, right?
- Here...
- I think...
we could get this right
if we use one more credit.
It's higher than 8.3 million.
If we make it
around 9.23 or 9.24 million...
- It's higher than 10 million.
Ten percent...
The answer is 9,240,000.
- That is incorrect.
- What?
The correct answer
is higher than your submitted answer.
It's really...
Should we pass?
- It feels like we could get it right.
- I know. It feels like that.
We have two left, right?
- We have one left.
- One?
Goodness.
- We really have one left?
- Yes.
If we use this,
will we earn nothing tomorrow?
We'll get some credits today.
We should.
But if we don't produce many lives here,
it would be the same.
- Ten million...
- We produced only one so far, right?
- Yes.
We might...
not be able to give them
because there's nothing to give.
Do around 14 million people
go to watch baseball?
Shall we go with 14 million
and cover for that range?
Shall we go with 14 million?
Shall we go for it?
It will be our last one, though.
If it says it's lower than 14 million...
Then we'll have to just guess
the answers for the rest.
Then we'll have the answer...
but no credits to carry on.
That would be so annoying.
It would be so annoying.
Then we'll have to leave with one life.
Is that the last one?
- Are we out of credits?
- Yes.
- We're in trouble.
- We can't make any more attempts.
- Fourteen million?
- Yes.
We'll have some for tomorrow, right?
Hold on.
- The last one.
- Wait.
- Fourteen million people.
Fourteen million.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is lower than your submitted answer.
(Answer: 12,312,519
Margin of error: 11,081,267 to 13,543,771)
This is the situation
we talked about earlier.
This is the worst scenario.
They could have counted that
as the correct answer.
We have the answer now.
We have the answer.
It was so annoying.
We could have answered it right
if we had credits.
It was a shame.
It was difficult to estimate
the exact numbers.
It would have been better
if we had more credits.
But it was really hard.
I know the answer to this.
They broke
the ten million attendance mark...
- last year.
- Okay.
They play 72 home games.
The average attendance is 20,000 per game.
The answer is 13,440,000.
- That is correct.
- Right?
- We were so close.
- So close.
Here's the next question.
- What would you regret less?
- Sixteen.
That is incorrect.
The margin of error is plus or minus one.
- Right.
- If it's more than 20,
the margin of error is five percent,
so that's too small.
Wouldn't it be more likely to be
around 15, which is slightly more unusual?
(How many outpatient visits does
an average person in Korea make per year?)
The answer is 17.
That is correct.
(The average annual number of outpatient
visits per person in Korea is 18.)
- We need to earn at least one.
- Here's the next question.
The answer is 4.3 million.
That is incorrect.
- Five.
- That is incorrect.
- The correct answer...
- What?
is higher than your submitted answer.
(Team White missed every question
up to the last one.)
Please. Just one more.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer
is lower than your submitted answer.
It's lower than 15.
Right.
There was a reason
why they gave 30 percent.
All production activities have ended.
You answered five...
- out of ten questions correctly.
- Goodness.
- It's really...
- You answered...
- one out of ten questions correctly.
- We know that. Don't tell us.
- What are we...
- It's really hard.
- going to do?
- What are we going to do?
One.
This is trouble.
Things are about to get serious.
We'll be blamed no matter where we go.
You answered
none of the ten questions correctly.
We know that!
Why are you saying it like that?
It was so hard.
- This is war.
- Yes.
- I'm upset.
- My pride is hurt.
Oh, this is a big problem.
We just couldn't figure out the answer.
But the issue is,
that means Team Blue will be the same.
Anyway, there aren't
enough lives right now.
There won't be any up for trade.
War is inevitable now.
We have already been struggling
to mine lives.
We have no choice but to go to war.
- Should we go to the hub?
- Let's go.
Okay. Let's head over.
The value of credits is already so low,
but it'll get even lower, don't you think?
- Yes.
- The value of diamonds went up,
and the value of lives was always high.
- Have you mined anything, you guys?
- What was that?
- Have you mined anything?
- Yes.
I did think Team Red would do well.
I'm just curious...
- Did you receive any lives?
Why would they give us lives?
- They're gone.
- What?
- Our total life supply.
- Our lives are gone.
So we thought...
they were redistributed,
with the skill development.
I think this might be it.
The answer to the question said,
- "Accumulated..."
- We were just talking about that.
Did you lose a lot of them?
- A lot.
- We lost a lot of them.
The Platform must've gotten it all.
We have to buy them from the Platform now.
It's all about diamonds now.
We're done for.
It might be beneficial for us
to buy lives right now.
Exactly. We need to buy lives.
- We're in trouble right now.
- It's Team White's time now.
You're not the only ones
who are in trouble.
We're in the worst position.
We don't even need a team anymore.
We're also kind of...
It's the same for us.
- Right.
- Our output today is awful.
We don't know what to do anymore.
Are they telling us to start a war
against Team White?
Are they telling us to start it?
But we don't have money.
- Let's put our money together.
- Should we?
I think putting our money together
does make sense,
but this is what I want to know.
Do we have enough to buy weapons?
Let's win without weapons.
We'll lose.
- If we lose, we go home.
- You want to gamble?
- Go home...
- Everything else right now...
- is too unclear.
- If we want to win the war.
That's not...
- a bad scenario.
- I think that might actually be okay.
One hit with our souls.
But isn't this too vicious?
Team White has the best conditions...
for starting a war,
but we're the ones going crazy...
and starting a war with them.
- This situation is so...
- Let's meet up again later...
after the announcement.
- Sounds good.
- We'll be back after the announcement.
This situation is so messy.
This is so unbelievable.
Here's the thing.
- There's not much being mined right now.
- Right.
Then they won't be able to sell any.
If so, Team White also dies.
Unless Team Black gets on our side,
it'll be best for them
to sell to Team White.
If their goal is to get more diamonds.
If they lock things up for us,
we'll just dry out and die.
Black will get all 200,000 dollars.
I see.
- This doesn't make sense.
- I'm jealous. Black will get rich.
If he gets
200,000 dollars without dying...
He must be so happy.
Good for you, Black.
Goodness.
After the Platform was introduced,
I think everything will go...
as Black wants.
If our relationship with Black goes bad,
we'll dry out and die.
We have to get along with Black.
We created this sort of public opinion.
- So the debt...
- This is an announcement...
- Oh, that scared me.
- from the Community Center.
Leader of Team White, please head
to the Community Center...
and collect the resources you produced.
They made an announcement.
So they won't have to go.
"Team White doesn't have to come."
- "You can just stay there, Team White."
- "You have zero."
- "You can stay out of this."
- It's so upsetting.
Leader of Team Blue,
please bring the resource storage...
and collect the resources you produced.
This is so unfair.
Why is this game so advantageous
for Black?
Let's go for now. We need the time.
This is basically for Black and White...
We need to take action right now.
(Community Center)
Please collect the lives
Team Blue produced.
(Resources produced by Team Blue, 1 life)
Leader of Team Red,
please bring the resource storage...
and collect the resources you produced.
They're calling everyone so soon.
Maybe nobody managed to mine anything.
We might've actually done quite well
by getting five correct.
Seriously. We're going already?
It is really so fast.
I think...
What's the point of our two teams now?
Why don't you have a bag?
Did you not mine anything today?
What should we do?
This isn't good.
Did they not mine anything?
Please collect the credits
produced by Team Red.
If you choose normal credits,
you will be issued three per question.
If you choose pollution-free credits,
you will be issued two per question.
We should cause some pollution.
I hope this can make a fatal impact.
I would like normal credits.
(Resources produced by Team Red,
15 normal credits)
(Resources After Day 4's Production,
White: 251 diamonds, 3 lives, 4 credits)
(Blue: 75 diamonds, 14 lives, 0 credits)
(Red: 55 diamonds, 5 lives, 15 credits)
(15 normal credits)
This game is too advantageous...
- for Black from start to finish.
- The whole time. It's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous.
- Why doesn't he have any demerits?
- Exactly.
- He doesn't even use lives.
- He has no risks at all.
Is that Black?
Is that Vector walking over?
- He's so...
- His walk is different.
- The way he's talking...
- He seems carefree.
Even the way he walks is annoying.
Hello.
Did you go from president to chairman?
The way you're walking...
I haven't gotten so much stronger.
- Pardon?
- I think you took all of the rights.
You took ten lives, right?
Why would I take ten lives?
They said
their total life supply disappeared.
I have no reason to take those lives.
Hasn't the damage already been reflected?
- They said it would be applied.
- I think so.
- They said so?
- It totally has been applied.
It totally has.
But Team Blue,
if your total life supply goes down,
your resources become more precious.
Then the value will go up.
It's bad for the community,
but it's good for Team Blue.
The good thing is that I don't
need to use up lives.
I secured about five for you.
Here's another piece of news.
One thing that gets activated...
is that the cost of war
becomes zero dollars.
So I partially blocked the prize...
from being cut down too much.
(Falsely saying the weapon dealer's rights
are similar to skill development)
- The cost of war is 0 dollars?
- I made it 0 dollars.
- Originally...
- But that's basically inviting us...
- to start wars left and right.
- I like that.
Oh, goodness.
So, the thing is...
Today is the day.
Something will happen for sure.
"Come on. Start a war."
That's what it sounded like to me.
"Do you want to attack first today?
Or do you want to get attacked tomorrow?"
It kind of felt...
like a threat to us.
He's inviting us to do it.
I felt that he set the stage
for us to do it.
But this is what I'm worried about.
I like the prize right now,
but we need to live with the worry...
that a war can break out so easily.
That's the downside.
That's not a bad thing for us right now.
I'm going to request it right now!
- He looks excited.
- I think it's zero dollars.
- That's what it said on the screen.
- Right.
So it was made for us to start a war.
We developed the skills...
Does a war start
once skills are developed?
My real goal
is the weapon dealer's profits.
Getting fees through the Platform...
is completely meaningless to me.
So I gave it a lot of thought.
Team Blue is worried...
because they're everyone's target.
If Team White starts the war first,
they'll issue currency
before they start a war.
If so, the war cost I carefully set...
will be lowered.
That's why I designed things...
so Team Blue would start the war first,
if there was going to be a war regardless.
"Many effects were activated,"
"and one of those effects
is that war costs become 0 dollars."
"I worked very hard to solve a question
to make that happen."
I made it sound as if it was good
for everyone.
It was to instigate a war.
We might have to start the war first
before people find out about this.
If the currency value goes up,
we'll be at a disadvantage when fighting.
We need to attack first
before they find out the cost is zero.
If not, they'll definitely figure it out.
Should I not tell them, then?
It would be nice if you didn't for now.
I do want to be fair.
If so, please make it seem
like I just didn't get the chance to.
- Of course.
- And that is actually the case.
- Right.
- Because I...
- We'll say so.
- Because I also...
need to maintain
my relationship with Team White.
Because the money...
I take home is up to Team White.
Let's hurry and go up.
It's better than staying here...
- and running into Team White.
- With Team White...
Were you talking?
From today, war is free.
Really?
It's here.
- How?
- Black said so.
Wasn't there a war cost?
- It's free now.
- It's just free now?
- Is it today?
It's a free war event today.
What I thought after seeing
that the war cost was zero was,
"Did Vector set this cost?"
"If so, he did such a smart thing."
"There will definitely be a war today."
I was cheering inside.
So we have to do it today.
- We have to do it today.
- Yes. It's today.
Those two won't band together
and attack us, right?
To gain what?
There's no real gain.
Hold on. What should happen
with this war, then?
Who has to start it with who?
Team White will have no choice
but to attack Team Blue.
- If they don't want to die.
But I don't think Team Blue
can fight against Team White and win.
- There's no way Team Blue can win.
- No way.
They'll come to us, right?
So in this situation...
if White attacks and Blue asks for help,
do we help them or not?
That's the key thing to think about.
We help them and say,
"Give us lives."
- Are we trading after lunch?
- Yes.
Then starting at lunch,
- they'll start talking trades.
- Right.
They'll probably bring up war too.
What I'm saying is...
I think war is inevitable.
As for our lives...
- Three?
- If the trade is for three lives,
- we won't need a sacrifice.
- Right.
If the trade is for two lives,
we'd have to sacrifice one person.
So our condition for Team Blue is,
we tell them,
- "We won't go to war with you."
- "We'll go to war with Red tomorrow."
- Right.
But by tomorrow,
- we'd only have 5 people.
- We'd be down to 5.
- If 2 from Blue join them, that's 6.
- Right.
All I have to say is this.
We'll take two lives and tell them,
"We won't attack you today."
"Help us attack Red. Let's team up."
- Today?
- Yes.
So if we get one and a half lives,
- we'd have six and a half lives.
- That's right.
We're attacking Team Red today, right?
- The plan is to attack Team Red today.
- Team Red... Right.
If Team Blue offers us just one life,
- "Then we're attacking you today."
- Right.
Don't say it like that.
Say they have no choice. They'll get it.
"Get ready."
We can't let our numbers drop to five,
unless we take one of them out first.
We can never let that happen.
- Right. We'd be at a disadvantage.
- A huge disadvantage.
- If we want to survive, we...
- Have to strike first.
We have to strike first.
We either attack you or them today.
- Right.
- Exactly. That's it.
- Those are our only options.
- That's what it comes down to.
We're between a rock and a hard place.
There's no way back.
- But here's what I'm unsure about.
- If we keep attacking,
what happens after that?
Do we have an exit strategy?
As for an exit strategy...
- We don't have one.
- We don't.
- But once...
- Once a war breaks out,
- it'll be war every day.
- Right.
But after that war,
- if Team White wants to win,
- Right.
- we have to strike first.
- Improving our chances...
- is the whole point.
- People on both sides will die anyway.
But if wars keep breaking out,
- I want to keep our numbers up.
- Right.
Let's completely reset for a second.
Could all the contestants collude,
so no one has to die?
Right now,
what we have,
what Team Red and Team Blue have,
- pool it all.
- Pool everything?
Pool it and split it among everyone.
That would keep us alive for just today.
- Today.
- Then just for today.
- We can all survive today.
- Is that 13 lives in total?
- We have 17 lives right now.
- We have 17.
If we divide them evenly,
- everyone should survive today.
- Right.
Then out of those 17 lives,
how many does Team Blue have right now?
Can we assume Team Blue has about nine?
- If we work backward?
- That many?
- Yes. I first thought they had nine.
- They might.
(Team Blue actually holds 14 lives.)
How many they have doesn't matter.
- Either way, they have plenty.
- Actually... Anyway...
- The total is at least 13 right now.
- Right.
- Right? So we can all survive today.
- Yes, that's right.
So if we reset everything...
and somehow divide the resources
among ourselves,
we can actually all survive.
- Then we don't have to start a war.
- Right.
- That's right.
- Right. Basically.
- Right.
- It's best to agree to keep this going.
We'll just have to go hungry.
(If all lives are shared,
everyone can survive.)
Let's go. I think we should meet Team Red.
Should I just knock?
- Yes.
(Team Blue requests a meeting
with Team Red.)
Yes?
Who is it?
- Coming.
- Is that Team Blue?
An alliance offer?
It's all about...
school, hometown, and family ties.
(Their proximity makes it easier
for the two teams to meet.)
- We...
- We'd like to talk.
- Should we talk?
- Should we go in?
- Team Blue?
- Yes!
Let's keep this quick and brief.
- White doesn't know the war cost is zero.
- They don't.
- But they'll know when trading starts.
- They'll know.
We need to reach
the Community Center first.
Otherwise, if Team White attacks,
- they'll issue a bunch, and it's over.
- Right.
- More issuance drives up the weapon cost.
- They'll drive it up.
If we're going to attack,
we should do it as soon as possible.
- First, we need to decide who attacks.
- So war is happening.
We also need to decide who attacks first.
We may be allies, but still.
What do you want to do?
Either way is fine with us.
But you hold plenty of lives.
- If you lose, you'll lose a lot.
- We have a lot to lose.
You'd lose a lot.
Should we attack?
Then we'll be allies.
If we lose today,
one person from our team has to leave.
- A life...
- A life for that person...
- We'll guarantee it, of course.
- We'll cover it.
- Got it.
- First...
- Let's make sure we meet at lunch.
- We'll meet and talk then.
- And bring some diamonds with you.
- Okay.
Let's go over there and talk first.
- Because we need to buy a weapon?
- Right. We need to buy one.
But...
But what do we gain...
by attacking Team White?
I'm not sure.
Right. Who knows? Maybe 50 or 60 diamonds?
But say Team Blue starts a war and loses.
Then we wouldn't get anything, right?
- All the lives go to Team White.
- Of course.
That would be the worst of the worst.
Why would Team Blue
form an alliance with us first...
or try to strike first themselves?
If Team White learns the war cost is zero,
do they think Team White will go to war?
Where did you hear about the war cost?
Black came over and told us,
but it could be a lie.
We can't trust anything.
We're the underdogs right now.
(Vector)
The war cost is...
zero diamonds.
The war cost has been set.
Please set the weapon cost.
The weapon cost is...
(Lunchtime)
Since the Platform was introduced today,
please purchase food through the Platform.
- Please enjoy your meals at your leisure.
- It's in the same place.
- Purchases go through the Platform too.
- So we buy through the Platform too.
- The store is on the Platform too.
- Right. So it's all the same.
- What should we do with these diamonds?
- Trading for Day Four will now begin.
- These won't fit in your bag, right?
- This concludes the announcement.
- Do we have a pouch?
- Just put them loose in a pouch.
Put them loose in a pouch.
Should we go get something to eat?
Let's go buy lunch first.
- This isn't a very appealing situation.
- Right.
There's no huge incentive for us.
- I never meant to start a war like this.
- Right.
- I'd only fight for a clear payoff.
- Exactly.
- Either wage a war of conquest.
- Right.
- Or fight for a greater cause.
I'd be fine with that kind of war.
- This would only leave us with a burden.
- Right.
Why should we do this?
Team Blue can't produce enough anyway,
so all those dependents are a huge burden.
Whether there are 3 of them or just 1,
they can't get the answers right.
Just kill them.
Hello.
Congratulations on the opening.
- Well...
- No, the store...
- We'll...
- Yes.
We'll do it.
- Do what?
- We'll attack.
- I see.
- In return,
if our prize money gets cut in half,
could you split the money equally with us?
War is still all you can think about.
Right. If that's what you mean...
Look.
If we start a war,
everyone will blame us.
Yes.
To be honest,
if anyone becomes a target of war,
there's no benefit unless it's Team Blue.
That's the cold truth.
- I see.
- Everyone else has far too few lives.
It's absurdly low.
- The war would get us nothing.
- Right.
I don't know. Let's eat first.
Let's talk while we eat.
But...
Did she put them in something?
I think she took the whole container.
It's Team White.
We gain nothing from running into them.
We really shouldn't run into them.
(Luna finally comes out of the dormitory.)
- Wait here for just a second...
- Where are you going?
So you can see?
You probably won't see them.
Hi.
Who is it?
- Luna.
- I see.
How is it going?
We're in serious trouble.
You got zero answers?
You got zero lives?
It's a complete disaster right now.
I keep wondering,
what are we supposed to do now?
War is our only option.
Sure enough, Team Blue...
couldn't mine any lives.
They mined zero.
Granted, these were verbal promises.
Team Blue hasn't kept its word to us.
It's happened far too many times.
Yesterday, we even gave them credits.
We even provided aid.
The day before, we had priority,
but we didn't get a single life.
After all that,
they still won't give us any lives.
Even if it wasn't a firm promise,
since we only have one life,
we truly can't give it to Team White.
Then,
the moment we say,
"We can't give it to you. Too bad,"
it would practically be
a declaration of war.
I kept getting that uneasy feeling.
- Hello.
I've thought it through,
- and I want to introduce tiered pricing.
- Exactly. That's how it should be.
- Tiered pricing.
Wouldn't that be more reasonable?
We're using tiered pricing.
Could you give us the room for a moment?
- Sure.
- Sorry, but Team Blue...
We got here first.
- Then Team Blue can go first.
- Let Team Blue go first.
- Team Blue is going first.
- Please step away for a moment.
- Over there. Go on.
- Sure.
- We need the prices to decide...
- I should close the door.
what we're going to eat.
This one costs 1,
and the rest cost 2 each.
They cost three diamonds, right?
I wanted to ask you both something.
He says this costs three diamonds.
Do you want to put it on our tab
until after the war?
Why would I run a tab...
No. It's in case we need weapons later.
But we're paying together with Team Red.
Something feels off right now.
Seriously, I think we might get attacked.
I don't think Team Red wants a war.
Team Red?
I feel like if they don't attack us,
they may not want a war. I'm not sure.
Earlier, they said...
"A war not targeting Team Blue
"is pointless."
That's what they said.
- Team Red said that?
- Yes.
I don't know how it came to this.
"Why attack Team White
instead of Team Blue?"
That's what they said.
"There's nothing in it for us."
That's basically what they were saying.
So little by little,
it's starting to make me nervous.
Should we just pay now? It's only three.
- Then let's pay now.
- Three diamonds, please.
Honestly, I'm giving you a great deal.
- Then buy some now.
- That's not what I mean.
You said we might need to buy weapons.
Shouldn't we buy them after the war?
We don't know what the weapons will cost.
If we end up being attacked,
are we going to buy bagels here
instead of weapons?
That's why weapons seem crucial now.
Then put it on our tab,
and you have to sell me one life today.
- Okay.
Okay. Then I'll put it on your tab.
- Got it.
- Yes.
- I'll do that.
- We should probably eat here.
But what's going on with them right now?
Even just to keep an eye on them,
- you're better off staying here.
- We should stay here.
Can everyone on your team survive?
- Us?
- Yes.
We're only covered through today.
- Just through today.
- Got it.
Today's going to be chaos for us.
For example, if Team Blue gives Black...
no lives at all,
there won't be any lives left to buy.
Then war breaks out.
Team Red! They're asking for Team Red.
And here's something even more shocking.
The total life supply has plummeted.
- The total life supply dropped?
- Yes.
Then the effect...
Black solved the question,
so the passive effect kicked in.
- I think that cut the total life supply.
- Yes.
So almost no lives are left to buy.
Should we get three mackerel?
Maybe two dumplings? Three? One more?
- What's this?
- Right now,
can we afford to eat this well?
- With what we have?
- No.
Won't the store close if war breaks out?
Right. You won't be able to trade.
That's why we want to stock up.
- Really? I want a corn dog.
- We're stocking up.
Eat. Go ahead.
- Then we'll each have a lunchbox.
- Right.
- That'll take care of lunch.
- We'll get ramyeon for emergencies.
- And some instant rice and ramyeon.
Fifteen diamonds should do.
You'll take 6 small Yukgaejang cups
and 3 bowls of instant rice,
plus 1 corn dog and 3 orders of dumplings.
(Team Red's lunch: 15 diamonds,
worth about 7,500 dollars)
I heard from Maillard that...
the total life supply dropped.
The moment the Platform was activated,
the total life supply dropped?
Let's discuss Team White's meal now.
Let's go.
We need to see how the Platform works.
Let's ask while we're buying food.
- The special costs 5 diamonds.
- Snacks cost 1 diamond.
- The special is five diamonds?
- Yes.
Four diamonds for a lunchbox.
- Four diamonds each.
- It's a little pricey.
Honestly, Team White pays a little more.
- I get it.
- I already knew that.
I know everything, you see.
I hope you don't hold it against me.
Of course. We understand.
This is capitalism at its finest.
- Let's pick our meals first.
- Let's eat. Food first.
- What should we get?
- I'll pay 18 diamonds for lunchboxes.
- Got it.
- Yes.
- I'm hungry.
- Me too.
- Seriously. I might pass out.
- My head hurts so bad.
Team White's special meals have arrived.
Food!
- We got lunchboxes too.
- Let's go!
- This is good.
That looks good.
- I'll clear this away.
- This is seriously good.
I'm seriously starving.
- Dig in.
- My hands are actually shaking.
I'm so hungry.
This is good.
When you eat after fasting,
- everything tastes really salty.
- Right.
- It does.
- We only fasted for a day.
- That's wild.
- Fasting makes every flavor intense.
- Lunchboxes are great.
- Yes.
Amazing.
I'm hungry.
Even if we get attacked,
stocking up isn't a bad idea.
I think it's a good call.
If we're doing this, let's spend it all.
Let's at least stock up on food.
- They have soft-boiled eggs too.
- Soft-boiled eggs.
- The soft-boiled eggs are good.
Then pick one I'm Real drink each.
I'll get blueberry.
(Team Blue spends 11 diamonds
on extra food.)
Eleven diamonds.
The supermarket was closed the day before,
and everyone had gone hungry,
so I knew demand would be huge.
Sure enough, everyone came running,
eyes blazing like they were possessed.
They waved diamonds, begging for food.
And with war possibly breaking out,
I'd quietly spread the word...
that the war cost was zero.
That sent everyone into crisis mode,
stocking up on emergency food
and war rations.
I'll put it in there.
All of it? What about the eggs...
Everyone's stocking up.
No one knows what'll happen.
- Everyone sensed it.
- They all already did.
They all think war will break out today.
But I'm stocking up as much as I can,
and while I can still get war supplies,
I need to secure and stockpile them.
We don't know how long this could drag on.
I think a war's about to break out,
so is that why I can't get food down?
I think that's happening to me too.
- We have to force ourselves to eat now.
- I can't digest anything.
Don't complain when you've got food.
- But I can't get it down.
- Are you okay?
This is miserable.
- But you have to eat.
- I'll get sick if I force it down.
- You need to eat while you can.
- I really think I'll get sick.
Where did Maillard go?
- Where did Maillard go?
- Over there.
What's going on with the talks?
Did your needs change?
I don't think we know yet.
We need to run the numbers.
- We haven't made up our minds yet.
- Because...
But if they start a war over there,
they'll go over and change...
the value of the currency for sure.
- They'll realize what we're doing.
- Right.
If we don't strike first,
- we won't be able to buy weapons.
- Right.
- You get what I'm saying, right?
So by the time trading begins here,
we have to decide.
- I know you're running the numbers.
- Right.
- But at least before trading begins...
- We need a decision fast either way.
- You need to tell us before trading.
- Quickly.
Okay.
They're pressing for a quick decision.
Team Blue thinks Team White
will print a fortune,
use it to gain a huge weapons advantage,
and then attack.
Why does Team Blue want a war?
What's their goal?
They want fewer mouths to feed.
Before the others get stronger.
Team Blue has a lot to lose.
Say we join in...
and get two lives.
Right. That's profit with no risk.
And the funny thing is, Team White...
might try to recruit us as allies.
- If Team Blue declares war on White...
- Right.
If we consider another option,
we side with Team White.
Would we get more out of that?
- That's funny.
- Yes.
They're seriously all checking each other,
each locked into position,
keeping tabs so no one can meet.
And everyone's so defensive.
It's the calm before the storm.
I saw Team Blue and Team Red
exchanging looks...
and waiting around.
I saw that. My first thought was...
keeping them from forming an alliance
in case a war breaks out.
We'll take this to our dormitory first.
But we should also...
- Finish eating and come upstairs.
- Okay.
What? They want us upstairs?
Do they want to talk?
Who are you siding with?
- Us?
- Yes. As allies.
Whoever gives us the better deal?
That's right. Exactly.
We'll have to think about it.
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The trading for Day Four will begin.
- We haven't even finished eating...
- From now on, all trades...
must go through the Platform.
If trading does not go smoothly,
- you may declare war.
- We haven't even finished eating.
Now I can't even digest my food.
The leader of any team seeking war...
must visit the Community Center,
pay the war cost,
and declare war.
- This is insane.
- Once war is declared,
all trading through the Platform
will stop immediately,
and Community Town will be
in a state of war.
Did they just mention the war cost?
Today's war cost is...
- zero diamonds.
- Zero diamonds?
The war cost paid...
- will be deducted from the final prize.
- They want us to do it.
What does zero diamonds even mean?
- They're telling us to fight.
- They want us to fight.
They seriously want us to go to war?
You will receive half...
of the losing team's total resources.
- Zero?
- Absolutely nothing.
- They're telling us to go to war.
- They really want a war.
This concludes the announcement
from Community Center.
(Now they know too.)
Are we going to war?
Some shady force is...
pushing everyone to start a war.
What?
We were absolutely sure...
the choice to start a war was ours.
We thought there would be a war cost.
So before paying the war cost,
we planned to issue currency.
That's why we kept carrying it around.
But now the war cost is zero.
So our whole plan fell apart.
With the war cost at zero,
anyone can start one on a whim.
If they wage wars indiscriminately
since it doesn't cost money,
and purchase arms,
that would lead to an arms race.
And we all know
what comes after an arms race.
A war is going to happen anyway.
Everyone would perceive us as a threat...
and would try to thin our numbers,
I thought.
So we need to team up
with either Team Blue...
or Team Red...
to prepare ourselves for a war.
It's scary.
- Has the trade begun already?
- Yes.
- Yes, it's time for trade now.
- Have you talked about it?
Now let's talk about it.
For now, we're in debt...
to Team Black.
- So we...
- Yes.
We need to talk...
between ourselves.
Are you going to trade?
- Now we can't trade anyway.
- If you ring the bell for trading later,
you can't trade with us.
You need to go through them anyway.
- You should talk to us first.
- You need to do it with us, anyway.
- How about talking with us now?
- However, the trading...
only takes place here,
and we can talk between us.
But we're supposed to talk to them first.
Can we come back later after that?
You mean with Team Red?
- We'll come back here.
- We'll be back right away.
Then,
you shouldn't meet with Team Red first.
You should come to us first
after the meeting.
That's a win-win, you know.
We're not going to trade with Team Red.
We need to talk between ourselves.
I know you're going to talk
between yourselves,
- We'll never trade with them.
- but come to us first later.
We can't trade with them anyway.
Aren't we being too naive
letting them go, just like that?
- They left in such a hurry.
- Right.
They need to talk between themselves.
- No, they're going to Team Red.
- They were watching Team Red.
They left as we made a move.
They're going to talk to Team Red.
What was that attitude?
If we hand over enough lives to them,
they're not going to wage a war.
That's their attitude.
That's never going to happen.
They're going to talk to Team Red.
- Not between themselves.
- Let's follow them now.
- Is that so? I'm sorry.
- We need to get in on it too.
Excuse me...
- I'll pay for the meal.
- You can buy something, Luna.
- Can I? I will.
- Yes, go ahead.
I'll make a purchase
and join you right away.
The thing is, if Team Red
intends to wage a war against us...
That is not going to happen.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
They don't intend to wage a war. As I see,
they have doubts about waging a war.
What?
What's that?
They asked if we're going to wage a war,
so I answered that we would.
This situation
doesn't look attractive to me.
If we can surely get something,
we can carry out a war of conquest.
If someone has to be
the target of our war,
it should be Team Blue.
He went in there.
What? Why?
There he is. He's waiting.
I know.
(The Trading Station is currently closed.)
(If you wish to declare war,)
(state that you will declare war.)
If he wished to wage a war,
he made a right choice of standing there.
I'm curious about with whom
he wants to have a war.
Us, in the first place.
If not, he has no reason to stand there.
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, if that's what he wants...
- Where are you going?
- The weapons left...
are only one for each item.
The first one who buys it can take it.
You can purchase an alliance too.
If one team purchases a weapon,
are other teams not allowed to buy one?
Weapons are classified into three classes.
For each class, we prepared one item.
And there's no limit on purchases
for each team.
Can teams participating as an alliance
purchase weapons?
Teams in an alliance can purchase weapons.
Thank you.
(Maillard came to check out
the rules regarding weapons.)
We should go.
But don't you need to trade?
You have no credit, don't you?
We can't make a trade...
- with just two, anyway.
- I see.
We need to collect a commission
through the platform.
We need to make a purchase
Then, would you like to leave
some credits with us?
I know. We should make a pre-trade first.
- We need to trade for about an hour.
- Then go ahead.
- Don't you think so?
- For now,
the other side definitely has caught on.
That's for sure.
If you want to purchase weapons first,
you need to go in.
All right.
- Share some lives with me.
- Okay.
Where are you off to in such a rush?
It was so heartless the way
they just walked away.
Why are they going in there?
So does he mean...
that Team Red bought weapons?
No, he wants us to buy them.
He says we can buy an alliance too.
That's why he tells us to do so.
He just checked out
how much the weapons are.
And he wants us to buy them?
- And they'd buy an alliance?
- We told them we'd do so,
and we handed over our lives.
For now, we'll have to handle
- the subsequent trading later.
- But can we trust Team Red?
Even if we can't,
there's no way to avoid them now.
If they declare war on us,
it's 6 to 3.
Otherwise, it's 6 to 6.
We have to be six, no matter what.
And she's following us now.
One from Team White came.
She noticed something.
Did you make a purchase?
- Purchase what?
- Did you buy food?
- They're buying.
- You need to hurry before a war begins.
Do you need
the kimchi flavored cup noodles?
- Or what do you want?
- I'll have the kimchi flavored ones.
- Kimchi flavored ones?
- Four kimchi flavored ones.
- Are these 50 in total?
- It's 50 in total. Right.
One, two, three, four.
- Take those.
- Okay.
One, two, three, four, five. Okay.
You have the paper, right?
We'll have to devalue the currency.
I think we need to devalue the currency.
So it's a preemptive strike.
Were they trying to declare war on us?
If you're anxious about that,
I'll stay here...
while you go talk to Team Red.
Anyway, the one who came in first...
Earlier, you said that Team Red
changed their mind.
Is that true?
They did change their mind,
but I talked to them again.
I told them we needed to declare war first
for the sake of currency value.
- I told them that.
- Did they agree on that?
We agreed to talk about that again.
Seeing that he was standing there,
I guessed they wanted to declare war...
and came in here first.
But if you still feel anxious about that,
- I'll be standing here.
- When Donkey was coming earlier,
he said, "All right.
Share some lives with me."
Yes, we'll join you.
- We'll join you.
- Okay.
All right.
Share some lives with me.
Okay.
But in case we lose,
are they going to share the risk together?
Can you check that out?
- I'll stay here.
- Okay.
You know what I mean?
So we... Wait. Let's recap this
so I can deliver it clearly.
We're going to declare war. That's a fact.
However, in case we lose,
are they willing to cover half
of what we forfeit regarding the diamonds?
- Exactly.
- Okay. I got it.
That's what you need to tell them.
We're going to pay for the weapons.
No. We need to charge them
for the weapons too,
- split exactly in half.
- That's right.
Split exactly in half. I got it.
For now, guard this spot.
You have to block Team White
from getting in first.
Okay.
If Team White enters first
and issues currency,
we cannot buy weapons, first of all.
For today, we need to stop them
from issuing the currency.
I'm not sure about
how much they went yesterday,
but I decided to block
the currency issuance today.
That's why I entered in the first place.
I wonder if...
- If...
- No, we didn't declare war.
- Did you declare war?
- No, we didn't.
Why did you do that?
We didn't declare war.
Then please have a talk with us.
How about alliances...
and sanctions?
- I want you to have a talk with us.
- Can't you talk with us now?
Exactly. Now it's time for trading.
- You mean regarding the trading?
- Yes.
For now, I need to check one thing out.
Then can one of you stay with us?
Will you stay here?
- Yes, I'll be waiting.
- Yes, please do so.
(Salt is left behind
to reassure Team White.)
Shouldn't we give some information
to Team Blue?
Well...
Regarding conditions for trading...
- They're out.
- You mean Team Blue?
They didn't declare war.
It's not as easy as it looks
when it comes down to it, I guess.
Wait, Genie is passing by.
I'll try to hold her back.
- How did it go?
- I need to check one thing out.
First of all,
we'll be the ones to declare war.
- Let's go.
- What's going on?
For now, one of us is taking over
the Community Center.
And lastly, before we declare war,
we need to check out
the details of this alliance.
We'll bear the risk of what we bet.
However, whether we win or lose,
we have the risks...
- of the cost of buying the weapons.
- Yes.
About that, we want you
to split the risks in half.
Instead, if we win,
we will split the spoils.
We're here
with that exact 50-50 concept in mind.
If you bear the risks,
we'll split those in half.
If there's no risk,
we don't have to split anything.
- That's right.
- That's how it goes.
We can split the diamonds with you.
And we need two lives.
All right. Anyway,
I get it. So it's 50-50.
- Then I'll declare war now.
- Okay.
- All right.
She asked us to be their ally.
And we agreed.
Because we happened to need lives
at that moment as well.
In fact, what matters more
than the profit split is,
in case Team White demolishes
Team Blue by a landslide,
Team White will stay
as a team of six members.
Considering the balance of power
at this moment,
if all members of Team White remain,
it's tough for us.
We need to cut down their numbers.
Why isn't she coming?
Here's the biggest problem we face.
If two of us are left...
or even only one of us happens to survive,
then honestly, from now on...
- So...
- Because we fully understand that,
we're talking to you first.
And we're going to make
a sacrifice anyway.
But that's not going to happen today.
If you can help us out a bit,
why don't you turn your gaze
to the other teams?
I'll go to Team Black. I'll ask,
"What happens to the credits?"
- That's what I'm going to try.
- Okay.
- You know...
- I'll go outside.
Don't you think you need to bring
diamonds with you?
- Diamonds?
- To buy the weapons for the war first.
I'll fill my pockets with diamonds.
I shouldn't let them see the boxes.
(Genie goes
to the Community Center again...)
(after negotiating with Team Red.)
- It's the same for you.
- Then wait a minute.
Genie, by any chance,
since we can't do anything at this moment,
why don't we listen
to what these people say...
- Will you listen to what we say?
- before we leave?
- Is that okay with you?
- All right.
- All right?
- Yes.
The quiz today was so tough.
So there are not enough lives
that we can get.
It's natural to think,
"Team White is going to attack for sure."
But we're not fools either.
We don't want to get involved
in a war and lose everything.
If you help us just enough
not to cross the final line...
Exactly how many lives do you have now
and how many do you need?
- How many do we need to give you?
- We need three of them.
Without those, we'll definitely die today.
To be honest,
you kept throwing away diamonds you mined
and keeping the balance running negative.
And after trading, the next day,
what if you go,
"We do not have enough diamonds today."
"We have no alternatives
other than declaring war."
- That's the situation we worried about.
- That's right.
However, the truth is,
let's say, tomorrow,
Team Red gets ten credits.
They'll have the initiative to attack.
(If we use a lot of credits,)
(we can eliminate...)
(a lot of lives.)
(It's a bomb.)
(Team Red has a skill
to destroy life reserves.)
Then, definitely Team Blue
will be the target.
We're going to raid Team Red.
Are you saying we ally...
- to attack Team Red?
- Yes.
- You mean we declare war?
They're up there.
Then they won't be able to attack us.
- And...
- Be quiet.
Please secure at least
a minimum of two lives for us.
- A minimum amount.
- You can sell them to us.
(Suggestions of trading 2 lives
and attacking Team Red)
- We'd appreciate that.
- Right.
In conclusion, Team White suggested...
to form an alliance and attack Team Red.
"Since Team Red has such a skill,"
"we might as well use
our numerical advantage..."
"to definitely wipe out one team."
"We need to keep their credits in check."
- For now...
- We're a team anyway,
- so we'll discuss it together quickly.
- Okay.
- She must be waiting for us.
- Sure.
She must be worried.
Please tell her
that she has nothing to worry about.
In the end, we're going to have
two lives out.
- It's the same for both of them.
- This is ridiculous.
You should've told me first.
How come you talked to them first?
I had a talk with Team Red first.
- Team Red said, as we requested,
- Yes.
regarding the weapons and the costs,
they'll split them exactly in half.
Instead, we'll also split
the spoils in half later.
All they need is two lives.
Team White wants to ally with us...
and attack Team Red.
It's because they find
Team Red's skill dangerous.
They think it makes sense
to seize their credits.
And they insist that in the end,
they only need two lives.
Now, we need to decide
which one we will attack.
Which team do you trust more?
To be honest, until a few minutes ago,
I definitely trusted Team Red.
Same here.
Until this morning,
I trusted Team Red, without a doubt.
However, they changed
their attitude in the middle a while ago.
That scared me so much.
If we look at this logically,
I think it's the right thing
to team up with Team White.
We just need to think about
what we ultimately want to walk away with.
Do you want to walk away with money?
Then we need to ally with Team White.
Do you need to be safe until the end?
If you think about that,
we need to choose Team Red.
Gosh, I'm so confused.
I like a winning game, no matter what.
You mean we team up with Team White?
However, even if...
- They won't go home, right?
- Team Red is attacked today,
- they're not going home.
- They have enough time to get things.
Tomorrow, they'll declare war on us.
Then shall we just ally with Team Red?
What do you think?
Honestly, I think Team Red
has the upper hand in power.
However, on the other hand,
that team is too powerful,
- so I'm hoping to weaken them.
- That's what I'm saying.
Anyway, one of those should go home.
I believe cutting down the numbers
is the right call.
The bottom line
is that we generated too few lives.
That's what I'm saying.
We need to reduce headcount.
- They need to go home.
- Let's ally with Team Red.
(The consensus narrows down
to an alliance with Team Red.)
You don't want to trade credits, do you?
- Trade credits?
- Yes.
The idea is on the table.
- There's a dissident.
- Shall we do that now?
Yes, if you want to.
Shall we go?
Now that I have opened Platform,
I want to see how it goes.
(Luna saw Team Red
trying to trade credits.)
- Look at that.
- Over there.
Excuse me.
I wonder...
how much progress has been made.
- We can't just wait forever...
- We've reached almost 90 percent.
Do you want to listen to her?
Do you want to talk?
- We talked earlier, but...
- Isn't Team Red in front of this place?
- They left.
- Team Red left with Team Black.
- Team Red disappeared.
- I wonder if Team Red...
- is trying to buy Team Black's skill.
- I know.
- As they're in a tight spot now...
- That's really dangerous.
How can they buy Team Black's skill?
If they buy it from Team Black,
they can get it for a diamond.
But he'll never sell it like that.
I suppose he won't sell it that way,
but if they buy the skill,
they can use it as a threat...
without using it.
They might go, "Do you want to ally
and wage a war?"
"We have this skill. See?"
That's what I'm worried about.
That's why I came here, getting anxious.
According to what Team White
said internally,
they're willing to send away
1 or 2 members.
That's what I heard.
We thought so yesterday.
We need to run the numbers too.
But if we lose one member,
we'll surely become
the target of a war afterward.
So for us, it's the right thing
to wage a war...
before we lose one member.
- Before you lose a member?
- If we lose one person,
there will be only five of us tomorrow.
Then if two teams team up,
we become a minority.
Other teams might think
that we can sacrifice...
at least one player.
However, the moment it happens,
our team starts tomorrow
as a team of five.
We'll be short of lives again anyway.
Then it's a war again.
And it's 6 to 5.
Rather than being 6 to 5
and keeping the war going,
we'd start with 6 to 6
and have a chance to win.
I thought it would be more advantageous
to drag them in first.
To be honest, what surprised me...
was that Luna was very hesitant...
to discuss reducing the headcount.
But I wondered, "In that case,"
"if there are casualties,"
"aren't we the ones losing our headcount?"
Let's say we ally with Team White
and we need to let one person go.
When Team White has that many players
and none of them wants to go,
we could end up getting abandoned.
That was what I thought.
But in this situation,
- it's a different story.
- Right.
Is the story going to be negative?
It could be either positive or negative,
but it will be different.
So we're going to get two lives,
and get one more,
- we're going to attack them.
- Team Red, I see.
Maillard,
isn't Team Blue waiting for us?
- Why?
- Team Blue,
being in a certain situation,
they're not taking any action...
- since we're not there.
- Shall we go there and see?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
The alliance...
- We'll go and check it out for a minute.
- Okay.
All right.
This is one of the things
we're concerned about.
In fact, in the case of Team Red,
even if they lose today,
none of them has to go home.
- Why?
- Why wouldn't they go home?
Can all of them stay
with only half of their lives?
They have enough lives.
Then they have the most lives.
Yes, they have a lot of those.
If that's the case,
they should have given us...
- the lives yesterday even more so.
- They should have.
We really had no credits.
- We had no credits.
- We used all, so we have zero credits.
Then you could have asked us...
- for aid.
- We could have made a transfer...
- and given you more.
- That's what I'm saying.
But you gave us only one.
It's because you gave us none.
You didn't give us any.
How could we give you more?
- We didn't get any.
- I get it.
- Stop it.
- When we say just one word,
- five of you swarm us.
- We can't do this.
When each of you says a word,
- we get five words back.
- I'm sorry.
In reality, the bottom line is that
we can't help...
- but feel intimidated by your headcount.
- Exactly.
Looking at your attitude as a whole,
- it's scary for us...
- That's right.
- to blindly believe in this alliance.
- I understand.
- I know.
- It's because...
there has to be some consensus that
we can eliminate a few mouths to feed...
if things go sideways within the team.
Otherwise, we'll end up in a situation...
- where our entire team gets wiped out.
- The reason...
why we're saying
we can't sacrifice any of us is this.
If a casualty occurs in our team,
we'll be the very first victims.
When we both have casualties
at the same time,
we can let go 1 or 2 of us.
But if we have to make
the first sacrifice today,
we'll be at too much of a disadvantage.
Even if that's true,
in the first place, the reason
we're even in this war...
is that the 5-3-3 setup
is just too heavy for us.
Then you can just do 3-3
to make it 6, can't you?
Right? As we play along this game,
Team Red might have the upper hand
if they go to war.
Then you need to ally with Team Red.
Team Blue is destined
to ally with someone.
So, you just need to align yourselves
with the winning side.
And today, it should be us.
That's exactly why we're making
a transparent proposal.
Yes. You can just use one enemy
to defeat another.
But in this situation,
if we ally with you,
- we become betrayers.
- Right.
- Team Red will attack us.
- Yes.
No, what I'm asking is, does betrayal
even play a part in this?
On the first day, you asked us
to ally with you. And the next day,
- you negotiated with Team Red.
- No, I'm saying it...
from the perspective...
- of Team Red.
- That's right.
We're the ones Team Red
would hold a grudge against.
- I'm not saying we're betrayers.
- No.
Team Red isn't a team...
- that gets swayed by emotions.
- Not by emotions.
- They only look at resources.
- They will attack...
whoever holds the most assets.
And that's us.
Anyway, when it's all said and done,
Team White is the only one
who can issue the currency,
- not us.
- Right.
Are you even in a position to give us...
a verbal promise
that you won't overissue the currency?
Actually, we gave you the verbal promise
from the first day.
Can you give us the exact numbers?
To be honest, that's something
we have no way of knowing.
We've been keeping our promise,
but you haven't.
However, when we talk...
- about why it ended up this way,
- We get it. Okay.
Team White never told us
there are limits either.
Then tell us our total life supply.
- We didn't know the limits either.
- It's everyone's last resort.
- It's because we don't know.
- All right. Then for now,
- since everyone is forced to lie,
- Everyone here...
- has told a lie.
- let's set that aside.
- Everyone here had told a lie.
- We haven't told a lie.
- Right?
- We haven't.
I mean, that team...
came to us asking to form an alliance
on the first day.
The next day, they completely ignored us.
They cut us off, but like absolute idiots,
we still handed over
our credits anyway. And then,
they ignored us again.
Isn't that, at the very least,
a violation of basic business ethics?
I thought they wouldn't listen to us
even if we persuaded them earnestly.
That wasn't an unacceptable claim.
It was only a threat.
From Team Blue's position,
it's the same for today and tomorrow.
They must have found us ridiculous.
Since there are only three of us,
we're already outnumbered.
We were already losing the numbers game,
but they kept pressuring us.
The moment I uttered a single word,
I got bombarded with five in return,
and it was honestly terrifying.
The feeling of being threatened
we felt at that moment...
was perceived as violence.
Are they already arguing inside?
The sign doesn't say it's occupied.
Why are you all standing at the entrance?
- It feels very cool here.
- Because it's cool?
- That's nice.
- What's going on?
First of all,
regarding our actual needs...
If you could just give us three minutes,
we'd like to take a moment
to evaluate our own needs.
We can totally understand
what you're saying now,
- and we totally can see your attitude.
- Okay.
- All right.
- We'll discuss it,
- and let's meet up in three minutes.
- All right.
What's going on?
I think we need to pull out of this.
Gosh, really.
Is this right?
I think...
To which team are you attracted now?
Honestly, I was attracted
to Team Red first.
Listening to them talk,
it seems they have a lot
of built-up resentment toward us.
They seem to have
so many grievances against us.
And to be honest,
I don't really understand their comment,
"If a casualty occurs today,
we'll be the first ones to go."
That's what I don't understand either.
Of course, that team should be
the first to produce a casualty.
The bottom line is, our basic premise...
is that we need to cut down
Team White's headcount.
Honestly, watching them swarm us...
with those numbers made me realize...
this is just too much.
If we side with Team White here,
it's an act of violence against Team Red.
I really can't go through this
now that I've experienced it myself.
We shouldn't do this.
This is too unethical.
- Right?
- Yes.
- We're on the same page, right?
We declare war.
Please state the target team
you wish to declare war on.
It's Team White.
Team Blue has declared war on Team White.
Today's war cost is zero diamonds,
so the payment has been completed.
- A war has been declared.
- The siren sounds.
- Team Blue has declared war...
- What?
on Team White.
Let's go.
They sided with this team here.
Wait a minute.
- That's right.
- Team Red and Team Blue.
- What?
- We're in a state of war.
As of this moment, Community Town
is transitioning to a state of war.
(State of war)
As we're in a state of war,
all functions of Community Town
are suspended.
When the siren blared,
I totally felt like
I was stabbed in the back.
I was just dumbfounded.
I thought I now had to kill them all.
The prize had no meaning anyway.
I will see who goes down first.
What kind of crazy stunt is this?
Are they seriously planning
to go on a reckless rampage?
If you're going to do this, fine.
Let's do it.
You're all going to die.
But we'll be the ones left standing.
Inside, I cheered. It's war.
I'm so happy now.
On the surface, I might look
totally strapped and anxious,
"No, we can't have a war.
What's going to happen now?"
"I finally opened the Platform today
with great difficulty,"
"but I couldn't make a single trade
and have no revenue. What do I do?"
That might be how I look to others.
However, everything
is happening just as I wish.
I think the justification
Pitou mentioned earlier is right.
What? Which one?
When she realized
the headcount of six people...
And honestly, I think it's right
to attack the side that's more desperate.
What makes them more desperate?
It's because the probability
that they go home increases.
Team White might come to us,
asking to ally.
That's possible.
It would be so funny if they came.
Right.
The ones who claim to be for peace...
are going around stirring up trouble
everywhere right now.
One minute they say they'll kill us,
and the next they're going to help us.
If you're going to be like that,
split up right now.
I can see through your dark intentions.
Our color has never changed.
We were always red.
We have to think about winning this.
- And Team Red...
- We have to persuade Team Red.
We just need to think about how we
can give Team Red a proper justification.
Or, at least, we need to tell
Team Red to do nothing about it.
Yes. We need to tell them
to do nothing or be on our team.
We can talk anyway
when we go to buy weapons.
We all need to buy weapons, definitely.
- No matter what.
- We all have to.
The prize doesn't matter now.
No.
- We all need to buy one.
- One for each.
We all need to get one.
The more expensive, the stronger it is.
Gosh, they have no idea
how expensive weapons are.
(The rule card on the detailed rules
of the war arrives.)
Please read this.
- I will read this for you.
- Okay.
The detailed rules of war.
Forming an alliance.
Team Blue and Team White that are
included in the declaration of war...
can ask Team Red to form an alliance.
If you want to form an alliance,
use the call button in your dormitory...
and request a meeting
at the Community Center.
When the request is accepted,
all the residents of the two teams...
visit the Community Center.
After the two leaders declare an alliance,
the alliance is formed.
If they win or lose the war,
the two teams, upon mutual agreement,
shall either submit or collect the spoils.
The quantity of the spoils of war
is determined...
based on the teams
in the initial declaration,
excluding the alliance team.
While the quantity is strictly based
on the parties involved,
the actual payment can still be made
together with the alliance.
During the state of war,
you can purchase weapons
at the Community Center.
There is one weapon per class...
available for Classes A, B, and C.
and there's no limit
on the purchase quantity per team.
Then if someone dashes and gets one
for each class, that's it?
That means it's first come, first served.
That's exactly right.
But our dormitory is located
in such a high spot...
when we need to run
to the Community Center.
Shall we wait with our shoes on?
(Springing to his feet)
The war cost and the weapon cost...
will be deducted
from the total prize pool,
equivalent to the value of the diamonds
at the time of purchase.
You can request a meeting
and purchase weapons...
after the announcement.
It would be great if we could just reach
a good agreement...
and fight without any weapons.
But Team White is desperate now,
so that won't happen.
But is Team White
really desperate enough to survive...
at the cost of cutting down
the total prize pool?
- Of course.
- Of course they are.
Let's say you're about to die today.
- Why would you care?
- Why would you increase the prize pool...
- for those left here?
- You don't have to care.
- Is that so?
- Sure.
I wouldn't do so,
if I'm going to die anyway.
- Would you die just like that?
- I wouldn't go that far.
- No, not before you actually die.
- You should try your best.
I don't care about the prize money
or anything else anymore.
This is going to be deducted
from our total prize pool.
Bring it here.
So we can't issue the currency now?
- No.
- We can't.
It's deducted based
on the current value of the diamonds.
- Yes.
- At its current value.
- How much is it per each now?
- It's 500 dollars.
- Is it 500 dollars?
- Yes.
Then 1,000 dollars will be deducted
if we get 2 of those.
Right.
Everything is going exactly
as I planned. This is amazing.
We can purchase weapons
during this state of war.
Then while we're at that,
someone can request a meeting
with Team Red...
and talk about it to them.
- Talk about what?
- Someone buys the weapons...
I hear something.
- They're announcing something.
- Get ready to press it.
From now on, you can request a meeting.
When the request is accepted,
you will receive an instruction.
- We need to call Team Red.
- And if you want to purchase weapons,
please bring diamonds with you.
- I think so, but...
- Not only the leaders...
but the residents can also purchase them
by paying with diamonds.
- Shall we go?
- You need to take diamonds with you.
- Come with me.
- Shall we go?
- Go.
- Hurry!
(Team White dashes
right after the announcement.)
Gosh, do we really have to do this?
Watch out!
- Does it mean we can buy them now?
- I guess so. We need to run now.
If Team White runs now...
and gets all Classes A to C,
it's over. Am I right?
Right. Why isn't Team Blue running?
Team White requested a meeting.
We will decline it.
The request for a meeting
has been declined.
They declined our request.
They declined it.
- I will be in front of the Center.
- Okay.
Why isn't Team Blue calling us right away?
Are they not really in a rush?
What are you thinking now, Team Blue?
What's wrong with you?
Get your act together.
We just started it, and we have to win.
Don't we need to meet
Team Red in the first place?
We should ask them to lend us
what they have.
- Gosh, wait a minute.
- Team Blue...
requests a meeting with Team Red.
I guess they don't feel
any sense of urgency.
Then tell them to suit themselves.
(Team Blue requests a meeting
with Team Red.)
- Accept it.
- We'll accept it.
Let's go to the Center.
Let's go to the Center!
How can we get it?
I hope they're not waiting there.
Gosh, this is tough.
(Team White arrives at the Center first.)
He's coming, right?
You're so fast.
(Occupied: Please wait.)
We'll purchase weapons.
The weapon costs are as follows.
(Weapon costs)
It's one each.
The weapon costs are 90, 70, and 40...
for Classes A, B, and C, respectively.
The total of the weapons
I designed today...
is 200 diamonds.
Since the total issuance is 400,
it's 100,000 dollars, which is half
of the total prize, 200,000 dollars.
A is 90, B is 70, and C is 40.
- We can only buy one each?
- Yes.
Let's buy everything.
- If we buy everything, we're all in.
- It costs 200.
It's 200. I know.
- Shall we buy them all?
- Yes.
(Class A Weapon, 90 diamonds:
45,000 dollars)
(Class B Weapon, 70 diamonds:
35,000 dollars)
(Class C Weapon, 40 diamonds:
20,000 dollars)
State the class of the weapon
you wish to purchase...
Shall we only buy Class A and C weapons?
and put the diamonds in the central box.
- We should buy them all.
- I agree. In the end...
This is so exciting.
We have to buy Class A weapon for sure.
- That's a must.
- Let's buy Class A first.
We'll buy Class A weapon.
You've purchased Class A weapon.
We'll buy Class B weapon.
No, my diamonds!
You've purchased Class B weapon.
We'll buy Class C weapon.
You've purchased Class C weapon.
Actually, we felt betrayed by Team Blue...
from the moment the war broke out.
The war they started was their way
of saying they'd cut off our lives...
even at the cost of the prize money,
so we were going to buy weapons
to teach them a lesson.
I definitely thought
we had to buy them all.
It meant we're spending 100,000 dollars.
But we had to buy them.
It'll be helpful.
If it doesn't,
we're spending 100,000 dollars
to show how scary the war is.
I didn't regret spending.
Since they started the war,
I thought we had to bear
that level of risk.
We don't care
if there's no prize money left.
That's what I thought.
So we bought them all.
I turned on the screen,
and it displayed
the accumulated weapon dealer prize...
as 100,000 dollars.
This is why
I went through all that trouble for.
That 100,000 dollars prize
explained everything.
(Vector's current accumulated prize:
0 dollars)
100,000 dollars)
Why are you declining my request?
I heard you tried to eliminate us.
My team?
Yes.
Your team is the scariest.
You always say you won't go to war,
so why are you trying to
eliminate us, who have nothing?
We were not trying to eliminate Team Red.
We wanted to secure three lives.
That's the same thing.
We don't need to go for a war
if Team Blue gave us...
three lives.
- You said you're planning to take...
- And we...
- three lives from us.
- It was a threat.
We never started a war.
You still...
- tried to...
- Why would we steal lives from you?
We're trying to get from them.
What are you talking about?
You were trying to start a war with us.
- Why would we...
- What's that?
We weren't trying to start a war.
- Team Blue did.
- Team Blue is claiming...
Team Blue and Team White are allies...
and they will start a war on us.
- Put yourself in our shoes.
- Okay.
Who's the better target
to start a war with?
So we think it doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't. If we start a war,
we'll be targeting...
- Team Blue.
- Why fight a pointless war?
- Let me tell you something.
- That war is...
- nonsense.
- So don't participate.
- Team Red doesn't need to.
- Don't participate.
- What's going on?
- Why fight a pointless war?
- What now?
- Let's not do this.
Are they disagreeing on
forming an alliance?
- We trust Team Red...
- We declined their request.
- Is that so? They caught him?
- I came first.
Yes, they caught him.
Anyway, there's nothing to lose...
by just watching today.
- That's for sure.
- And you have your credits...
- that you made today.
- One will end up at a loss.
- You can just wait for that.
- And...
you might need to give out your resources,
but it's better to just watch
and secure them.
They're not earning any lives.
- But we'll take from them.
- We'll take it away from them.
- If we eliminate in the future...
- If you take it away, Team Blue...
will be eliminated
and when they become smaller,
they won't be able to supply lives
even more.
- Will they?
- Yes.
- I don't think there'll be a difference.
- It'll be similar.
There won't be a huge difference.
- Our production...
- It'll be similar.
- We have better efficiency.
- Team Blue will be similar.
We're far better.
We can produce far better
if you keep us six alive.
Are we okay to meet up like this?
- It's not allowed, right?
- Let's go to the Community Center.
- Let's talk further.
- But...
- No, wait.
- Wait. There's no decision made.
- I'll hear you out.
- Okay.
- Hear me out.
- Why?
- First of all...
- Okay.
- I get why they're so desperate.
- Seriously. Yes.
Earlier, they were saying
we should attack Team Red.
My goodness.
- Team White gets tainted everywhere.
- Exactly.
You're the whitest person here.
- What happened?
- Yes, you are.
What's going on?
- We're going to meet Team Red.
- Together with Team Red...
Trying to persuade
Team Red not to fight...
- and just go with 6 to 3.
- Team White is trying.
(Maillard arrives at the Center first.)
Team White is sneaky.
(Occupied: Please wait.)
Team Red is here.
They're definitely allied.
I'm sure.
Our first goal was...
- getting three lives without a war.
- We didn't want a war.
To persuade on getting three lives,
we were giving examples
on what different things we could do,
and attacking Team Red was
one of the examples.
They're trying to convince you
by twisting what we said.
- So it was hypothetical.
- Yes!
If we were to start a war,
we would've had pressed the button.
Team Black is the worst.
He is the one who made the war cost zero.
He released the skills,
so the war cost became zero.
He's trying to make
the war go on indefinitely.
- Team White is already inside.
- What?
- They're inside.
- They are?
We should've run immediately.
- To buy the weapons.
- Yes.
Team White ran for it.
Of course. We're in a state of war.
And all they've got is diamonds.
They definitely ran for it.
(Team White bought all the weapons
with 200 diamonds.)
We used up...
- all the prize.
- Yes.
- But I'm fine with it.
- Are we the villains?
- It doesn't matter. They started a war.
- I am...
originally a person who lives modestly.
Maillard, what's going on?
We need to go to a meeting.
- Everyone must go.
- Everyone must attend.
Why is he stuck there?
If they don't secure allies here
and buy weapons,
they have no way to survive.
- They're out.
- They came out.
It's time for Izaha to come.
You should come here now!
Izaha!
- We have money to buy weapons.
- Okay.
More than the two teams combined...
(Izaha goes to the Center belatedly.)
- Where's Izaha?
- He's being held back.
I tried calling him many times,
but I guess he's going to finalize
the matter.
Do we all need to gather?
- Yes, so we waited.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
Come on, Izaha.
We want...
to be an ally with Team Red.
Team Blue and Team Red formed an alliance.
Two teams will be in a war together.
If you wish to purchase a weapon,
please request.
- We wish to purchase weapons.
The remaining weapons are as follows.
(Weapon cost)
- They bought them.
- They purchased them.
They already bought them.
They're all sold out.
How could they buy them all?
Wait, they spent that much?
- Were they that rich?
- But...
it's a bit underhanded.
- I know.
- Right?
What are they, track athletes?
How did they get there so fast...
and buy up all the weapons?
I thought there'd be at least one left,
but they took them all.
But I can't really get a sense
of how powerful the weapons are.
They were all sold out.
They're so ruthless.
They say they want peace,
but how much did they spend on weapons?
I had no intention of purchasing weapons.
I was skeptical.
The prize money gets deducted, right?
We're all here...
to win the prize money.
Rather than all of us
having our prize cut,
let's just agree not to buy weapons...
before the war even starts.
We should have at least said,
"Let's not cut the total cost."
I regret...
not being able to stop it until the end.
(Pitou, Actress)
(Battlefield)
Eliminate them all. Are you confident?
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Eliminate them all.
- I'm scared.
- It's scarier at night.
- My gosh.
- What's all this?
There's a strange building.
It's grand.
(The battlefield looks very different
from the Community Town.)
It's so eerie it actually feels...
like we're at war.
The abandoned building...
made it feel a bit overwhelming.
I don't know why, but I was fired up too.
- My gosh.
- What's going on?
- What's this place?
- No!
- What is it?
- Why?
(Entering the battlefield)
- What's this?
- It's amazing.
It's cool.
The atmosphere there...
was immersive.
It looked like an old cathedral...
or a church with stained glass.
Something is about to happen here.
Things have already turned out this way,
so if we want to thin the numbers...
and coexist with whoever's left,
we have to win this game, no matter what.
Are you okay with scary stuff?
There's nothing scarier than losing lives.
Why are these people all so cool?
Let's go.
Honestly, I didn't think of losing.
Today, I'll teach them a lesson.
I'll crush them.
We just win. No matter what.
We're stuck
between a rock and a hard place.
If we lose here, we're done.
We got all the weapons ready.
Now it's the final showdown.
Let's give it everything we've got
and survive.
Residents, welcome to the battlefield.
Today's battle is...
the Proposition Race.
- Proposition Race?
The Proposition Race is a game
where players find cards...
with various words
within the time limit...
and use them to create true propositions.
The Proposition Race consists of...
a 45-minute 1st half
followed by a 45-minute 2nd half.
During each round, residents must search
the underground area...
and secure the cards they need
to make propositions.
However,
no items other than proposition cards...
may be taken out of the underground area.
Proposition cards consist of
country-name cards,
comparison-value keyword cards,
adjective cards with predicates,
and particle cards containing
"is," "are", "than,"
and other grammatical particles.
The location of each card is fixed.
It's not possible to resubmit...
the same proposition
by changing the positions of the cards.
However, propositions using
different predicates will be recognized...
as separate correct answers,
even if they deal with the same fact.
- Find the diamonds.
- We need lots of particle cards.
Let's get as many particle
and comparison-value keyword cards...
as possible.
Don't we just have to sweep them all?
Once a proposition is complete,
each team can enter
its proposition submission booth...
and submit it.
A correct proposition earns one point,
while an incorrect proposition
loses two points.
Duplicate propositions...
do not earn any points.
All points are tallied
and revealed only once...
at the end of each half.
Whether a submitted proposition
is correct...
is not revealed at the time of submission.
Making the right guesses is crucial.
You lose points for incorrect answers.
All submitted proposition cards are
discarded regardless of whether...
they are correct,
while proposition cards that have
not yet been submitted during...
the 1st half can be used in the 2nd half.
In addition,
a maximum of two members from each team
may enter the underground area at a time.
Members may be freely replaced.
However, cards being physically carried
by a member...
cannot be taken from them.
Each weapon can be used only once...
throughout both halves.
To use a weapon, ring the bell
inside the proposition submission booth.
(Weapon used)
We need time to combine the cards.
Once you gather enough cards,
come up with them.
- Let's spread them out and work on them.
- Then...
One from each team should...
- come up, switch, come up, and switch.
- Okay.
- I'll go downstairs.
I'll go.
- It'll come down to stamina.
- Right.
- Okay.
- I took a look,
and I needed to go from my team.
The other guys are quite old,
and the ladies are delicate.
I have to do the search.
I was fine with running.
All I needed to do was
bring the cards upstairs.
Genie and Pitou looked tired...
whenever we took the stairs.
So I decided to do the running.
In the first half, we must secure
as many cards as possible.
- Look.
- Sweep them all.
- We'll bring them all.
- Okay.
But here's the problem.
You must go through the cards quickly...
and tell us what we're short of.
- Okay.
- Then we'll look for those.
Say that things turn out for the worst,
and I get exhausted.
- You must get ready to run.
- Of course.
I'll be all set to run again
after a break,
- so I'll switch right away.
- Okay.
But in return,
those who replace us shouldn't think,
"I'd better work hard and find
as many as possible."
Move out once we seem better than before.
- Okay. We'll sub you just for the break.
- Okay.
Get greedy, and it'll get messy.
- We'll fail at communicating.
- Correct.
- How far...
- We only need about 30 seconds...
- to one minute of rest.
- Got it.
We must crush them with our stamina.
You two are very important.
(Team White's search team is
Boss and Paul.)
- How complicated.
- That team will switch a lot.
- Right, the stamina.
- But that's not good.
It's not good at all.
We should each be in charge of
that particular role.
Those who are smart, use your brains.
Those who are athletic, run.
Let's do this!
- We can do it! Let's gather up.
- We can do it!
- Go, White!
Shall we do a team cheer?
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
- Go!
The first half of the Proposition Race
will now begin.
- Let's go slow, as if jogging.
- Okay.
Be careful.
(The Proposition Race begins.)
(First half)
Let's go.
- Our team was slower.
- Oh, no.
- I know, right?
- Catch up to them.
(Team White's search team takes the lead.)
"I have to run faster than them."
"Let's crush them fast."
Over here?
(Underground area)
This is scary.
It was really dark.
Things were all over the place.
It was such a mess.
Had it been the usual me,
I would've never gone in there
because it felt haunted.
But that didn't matter here.
Even if a card was beneath the ghost,
I was going to find them all.
(1 proposition card)
What a huge mess.
Honestly, the underground area wasn't big.
Make a wrong move,
and the tables could turn.
We had to take every card
so the other team...
couldn't do anything.
We needed to win on speed.
We needed to overwhelm them.
Goodness.
(His hand is full of proposition cards
in no time.)
(1 particle card)
(Paul sweeps the cards with crazy speed.)
(1 proposition card)
- Oh, dear.
- I'm sorry.
Take it.
(1 proposition card)
Searching and such is what I'm good at.
I have an edge over the civilians.
(1 proposition card)
Corners, angled areas, edges,
door frames, windowsills, and more.
Booby traps could be hidden there.
If we don't check,
the operations team is done for.
Searching as I did before
helped me find the cards.
How dirty.
(1 proposition card)
(Groaning)
(Boss finds a card
in every spot she searches.)
Move, please!
(1 particle card)
(Donkey found a mysterious box.)
What's this?
It had 3.14 on it.
I've memorized pi, 3.141592,
and the box had four blanks to fill.
I unlocked the box right away.
(Lower)
I had a rush of dopamine.
"This is what I came here for."
I felt super smart.
(After wandering around, he reaches
the room at the end of the hall.)
I went to the master room,
and it was just empty.
(Donkey, Stand-up comedian)
Just when I was about to leave,
thinking there was nothing,
there was a sledgehammer.
I looked at it, thinking,
"Why is a sledgehammer here?"
Right next to it were black boxes.
"I need to crush them.
I need to break them."
I took the sledgehammer and smashed them.
I opened the box,
and it was filled with cards.
I thought, "Nice,"
and kept smashing the boxes.
(Proposition cards, particle card)
(Donkey destroyed the boxes
and secured a bunch of cards.)
- This is tough.
- Okay.
- That's a lot.
- What's with this stack?
- What are all of these?
"Than."
- "Than."
- Let's decide on one country first.
There are so many Greece cards.
- Greece, Japan.
- Look at all the Greece cards.
- There's quite a collection.
- The two should give us some,
not deliver it to us altogether.
- Of course.
- Can't we look at what it is?
- This is right, isn't it?
- He found a bunch.
- Greece.
- Greece is...
Greece. Over here.
"Smaller. Larger."
- No, it's over here.
- The comparison-value cards are hard.
There's nothing about Greece.
Germany has a higher
national competitiveness than Greece.
Shall we take these?
- For now...
- Make more for now.
- Let's write it down.
- Okay.
Take these first.
(Submitting the first proposition
as soon as it's complete)
(Germany has a higher
national competitiveness than Greece.)
The submitted proposition
has been registered.
(Germany: Ranked 8th, Greece: Ranked 13th)
(Proposition Race, Blue: 1, White: 0)
(Greece has a lower
Comparative Price Level than Sweden.)
The submitted proposition
has been registered.
We can receive the cards from here...
- without stepping outside.
- Right.
Let's do that.
They must be bringing a bunch.
Probably.
I'm anxious.
Hey.
My pants are sliding down.
(Boss dumps out a huge pile of cards.)
- I'm leaving.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- I'll take them.
- Give me one.
- Wait.
- Let's sort them out first.
Okay.
- What a collection.
- The particles go here.
They overlap. Let's gather them together.
Give me the countries.
"Has." Okay.
Chile has a higher Gender Inequality Index
than the United States.
But that's a guess.
For now, let's go with something
we're certain about.
Land area. That's easy, right?
- Okay.
- Let's start with that.
All right. Larger population.
- The US has more than Korea.
- Should we put it there?
- Right.
- Let's not use Korea. Korea is easy.
- Korea.
Sweden. Sweden's population.
The US has more than Sweden.
- The particles are over there.
- Where's population?
- Population.
- Population. All set.
Next. Obesity rate.
Japanese people are the skinniest. Right?
- Japan. Obesity rate.
- But...
Of course, Chile has
a higher obesity rate than Japan.
Chile?
Japan has the lowest obesity rate
in the world!
Got it.
Leia has a lot of general knowledge
and common sense,
and she was just so good at everything.
- Look, guys.
- Okay.
Korea has a higher suicide rate...
- than Turkiye.
- True.
"Turkiye has a lower suicide rate
than Korea."
- That works too.
- It works.
So look at the board and see what we have.
Once the contrary proposition is complete,
- submit the proposition.
- Okay.
Sweden's Gender Equality Index...
- must be higher, right?
- It is high.
Right? Than which country's index?
- Japan has a low Gender Equality Index.
- Which country would have a low index?
- It's still low in Japan?
- It's always been like that in Japan.
- Japan.
- Japan. All right. There.
Leia and I were in charge of
putting together the propositions...
as we played a major role
when it came to knowledge-based quizzes.
Luna, who's very thorough and detailed,
was to check every word of it.
She'd check if we overlapped anything.
Honestly, I'm not that knowledgeable.
Instead of putting together
the propositions,
I focused on organizing the keywords
and arranging them by type.
Keeping them organized could help them
make propositions faster.
So that was my focus.
"Korea has a higher Internet usage rate
than Chile."
- It's higher.
- Higher.
We have more cards for "lower."
Let's switch them out.
Yes. It should go like this. Right?
- Yes.
- Can we go with this?
Go with a certain one.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
(Team White submits
their first proposition rather late.)
We'll use Class A Weapon.
What's going on?
- What's this?
- Right.
Team White has used their weapon.
The proposition submitted...
- with the weapon will earn...
- What is it?
triple points.
- Okay.
- What?
I thought anything could happen then.
I was worried that
we could end up losing...
because of the weapon
at a critical moment.
"Chile has..."
"a lower Internet usage rate than Korea."
Here's our submission.
The submitted proposition
has been registered.
(White earns 3 points
thanks to Class A Weapon.)
- Here.
- Are you certain?
- Yes, we are.
- We're certain.
A higher population density...
(Greece has lower household spending
than Switzerland.)
"Lower household spending?"
No.
We should go with "less," not "lower."
(A proposition is considered false
if its predicate is incorrect.)
- This is the wrong predicate.
- What do you mean?
We have to use "less," not "lower"
for this proposition.
- This is wrong.
- Okay.
- Greece... Yes. "Less."
- Let's go with that then.
That could've been bad.
"An average Greek household spends
less than an average Swiss household."
Here's our submission.
"Switzerland has a lower
infant mortality rate than Mexico."
Take these cards.
(Switzerland has a lower
infant mortality rate than Mexico.)
(Switzerland: Ranked 8th,
Mexico: Ranked 1st)
We've got Greece and Japan...
Greece and Japan?
(Japan has a higher GDP than Greece.)
(Japan: Ranked 3rd, Greece: Ranked 15th)
"Switzerland has..."
"a higher Comparative Price Level
than Mexico."
- I see.
- That's...
(Switzerland has a higher
Comparative Price Level than Mexico.)
(Switzerland: Ranked 1st,
Mexico: Ranked 13th)
- The UK and Korea. Dust concentration.
- Korea...
- The UK and Korea.
- Yes.
It has a higher GDP...
than Greece.
Great. Next.
Japan and current account balance.
Hold on. Instead of going with
the current account balance for Japan,
let's go with life expectancy.
It has to be high for Japan.
"Greece has a lower
Comparative Price Level than Sweden."
Things must be a lot more expensive
in Sweden.
- I have no idea.
- He's the best.
This is amazing.
This is crazy.
I can't find "higher."
Then let's go with "lower."
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- I can't believe this.
- We had a machine on our team.
- He's...
- like a machine. Is he AI?
- Hurry.
He's good.
The suicide rate.
- Korea.
- The one for Korea, right?
I just need a postposition.
We definitely need a lot more particles.
Yes. We have to look for those.
Smaller cards.
Hey.
Could you look for particles?
- I'm sure I can find some.
- Particles.
- We got it.
- There's some.
- Bring back more.
- Should we try that?
(Salt runs out again
after giving them more particles.)
Darn it. I'm tired.
- We can do this.
- We got this.
I'm so tired.
Come on. I can't find anything now.
- We can't. We found everything.
- Now...
There are no more cards left now.
I keep looking, but there's none left.
None means none.
(1 proposition card)
Darn it. I don't know how to crack this.
(Boss is feeling small
when it comes to a quiz box.)
Paul.
- Paul.
- Yes?
Could you crack this for me?
Crack it for me. I don't know.
(In what year
did the Berlin Wall come down?)
I can't crack it either.
Good luck.
Actually, I thought
Boss and I had a better strategy...
and were better equipped physically...
to find the cards than Teams Blue and Red.
But when we found
a lot of boxes with locks,
it was difficult for us
to crack the codes.
We decided to hide all the boxes
until we got someone on our team...
who could solve these questions.
Okay.
(Paul and Boss hid them
all in the same spot.)
Paul. I'll go and check in.
Give them to me.
- Okay. Run.
- Yes.
Okay.
I thought we had great teamwork.
We kept calling each other's name
and checked on each other.
When people get tired,
they easily lose their focus.
But since she was in the special forces,
she was clearly great at running.
She was also fast.
Leia.
- When you go in,
- Yes.
- there's a room on the left.
We can't open those boxes.
So you have to go.
- We have to crack the codes?
- Yes.
Go and turn left.
(Dispatching Leia to solve the quiz boxes)
Go and turn left?
- Paul.
- Yes.
- Come here.
- Okay.
Look. This is what we have.
Next...
(Uncovering a pile of boxes)
- The question mark...
- Okay.
- I must solve them to take the cards?
- Yes. Stay here.
- I'll bring everything here.
- Okay.
We're running out of words and predicates.
It'd be nice to find more predicates.
- They might be in the box.
- Okay.
- I got most of them here.
Paul had stacked up 3 to 4 boxes.
No, there were 4 to 5 boxes stacked up.
He wanted me to solve the quizzes.
Our life was on the line by then.
I felt a great sense of responsibility.
(In what year
did the Berlin Wall come down?)
(The box is open.)
(In what year did World War I break out?)
No more. Wait. No. That's not it.
Over there.
I got it.
Where? There's one here too.
(She finds a proposition card
in the moss-filled water.)
- Great.
- I'll get back out there.
- I'm fine.
- Get some rest.
- It's okay.
- We need to find smaller cards.
- I...
- Are you all right?
- I searched everywhere.
- Yes.
My gosh.
(Salt has been running around
without switching with anyone.)
They didn't touch the cards in the water.
So I dipped my hand in
and found some cards.
I got those places.
(Maillard switched with Donkey earlier.)
Why are there so many keys here?
I'm going to get to them.
I'm just keeping them here.
- You can't do that.
- No. I'm getting to them.
You have to solve them one at a time.
You can't hog all the boxes.
- That makes no sense.
- Fine. Go ahead.
- Donkey.
- Yes?
Did you see the phone number
for Camellia Snack Bar?
Yes, I did.
This way.
Is it here?
There it is.
It's 1311.
(They find a clue for the lock
from a thrown-out flyer.)
- Nice.
- My gosh.
There's only one card inside the box.
Darn it.
I should take them.
(Leia opened all the boxes she could.)
- That's...
- Paul, do you have more cards for me?
No. Give them to me.
- Give them to me.
- I solved all the quizzes over there.
Okay. Give them to me.
Okay. I'll take them with me.
I have to put together sentences.
Then I'll switch out.
Gosh, what could this be?
(There are locked boxes
she wasn't able to solve.)
Wait.
I know the answer.
"Wait. The phone number
of a Chinese restaurant?"
"How do I know that number?"
I thought about it
and remembered the sticker on the wall.
I ran out and checked.
It did say Golden Chinese Restaurant.
I went back in
and cracked it open right away.
My gosh. You're a genius.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
"What number goes in the question mark?"
(What number goes in the question mark?)
Okay.
Five, nine...
Try 9839.
There was an addition
of four-digit numbers.
When you overlap the numbers,
you get the answer.
I like going to escape rooms.
So I've done many quizzes like that.
We should have brought in Hamlet.
But we didn't have enough time
to stop and think about strategies.
(Hamlet is in charge of
arranging the cards efficiently.)
We have time.
Can you check if this makes sense?
This one.
Yes, Korea beat Japan.
- Right?
- Yes.
Our GDP went up.
Here's our submission.
"Greece has a lower GDP than Korea."
- Without the cards...
- Right.
- He's back.
- Gosh.
- I couldn't find any particles.
- None?
- There aren't any left.
- Oh, no. What do we do?
- But...
- Should I go and check?
- No. I'll go back.
- Okay. Are you okay?
- This is bad. I'm nervous.
- Oh, no.
They have a lot of black cards.
- They have so many black cards.
- The black cards are...
- the key.
- We can say the usage rate is lower.
- Right? We did one with Korea.
- Should we try that?
Right. Australia recently banned minors...
- from using social media.
- Right.
- That's true.
- Let's make one.
Japan...
- It's lower, right?
- Yes.
The Internet usage rate...
"Australia has
a lower Internet usage rate than Japan."
Here's our submission.
(2 points deducted, Australia:
Ranked 4th, Japan: Ranked 14th)
The second half will get super intense.
Do you think Korea has...
a lower World Happiness Index
than the Netherlands?
- It has to be lower.
- It would be, wouldn't it?
Are people in the Netherlands depressed?
- People are free-spirited there.
- We shouldn't submit...
uncertain ones in the first half.
Cannabis is legalized in the Netherlands.
Wouldn't they be happy?
They must be. Right.
- I think the index will be higher there.
- I think so.
Let's complete it, but we won't submit it.
(First Half)
- It's over.
- The first half...
of the Proposition Race is over.
You can't touch the proposition cards now.
- You can't submit propositions either.
- We can't touch them.
- Residents in the basement,
- Ten, twelve, thirteen...
- please come back upstairs.
- We should have about 16 points.
- So...
- That's...
It's over? Okay.
I got it.
- Gosh, I'm exhausted.
- Get some rest.
If we got everything right,
we should have 12 points.
They used the weapon earlier
and earned three points.
Their score is probably higher.
Here are your current scores so far.
Let's go. Please.
Team White.
(Mid-Game Scores: Blue, White)
- Fourteen points.
- What?
- One of them was wrong.
- We got one wrong.
The one we didn't submit must be correct,
and we got one wrong.
Team Blue.
(White: 14)
- Nine points.
- What?
- It's okay.
- So...
- did we get a few wrong?
- It's okay.
We both got one wrong.
(Japan has a lower
World Press Freedom Index than the US.)
I need to tell Izaha to get a grip.
Not submitting false propositions
is the most important.
One false proposition
would put us three points under.
We lose two points
for each false proposition.
When they score 1 point
and we lose 2 points, the difference is 3.
He needs to know that.
I think everyone is rushing
to submit the propositions.
I believe
reviewing the propositions thoroughly...
and not submitting any false propositions
is the most important.
They're five points ahead
with Class A Weapon.
We can't submit
any false propositions now.
We need to submit
a lot more propositions...
to make up for this difference.
Buying the weapon was the right call.
We can stay ahead with the weapon.
They will be under more pressure
in the second half.
The second half will begin shortly,
and your tables will be switched.
Isn't it better to search tight spaces...
- than large spaces?
- That's better.
Then I'll start from the front
on the left side.
You can move forward
from the back on the right side.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- Let's start from opposite ends.
- Yes. Okay.
What do you need the most?
All of the black cards are important.
- Pick up all the black ones you can find.
- Black ones...
Let's not come upstairs unless we have to.
It's better not to stay there
as long as we can.
They took their time before coming up.
So they found a lot more cards.
Let's find ways to keep
as many cards as we can on us.
We should come up
only we can't hold anymore.
The second half...
of the Proposition Race begins now.
Let's go.
- You got this!
- Let's go!
My gosh. They're so fast.
(The speed difference between
the two teams is starting to show.)
Darn it.
Let's kill them all.
(Paul and Boss take a line each
and start searching for cards.)
(They acquire a big load of cards
in no time.)
(The search team of Blue and Red
arrives after them.)
(Maillard starts with the box
in the room at the far end.)
(He obtains ten-something cards
in an instant.)
(Maillard grabs
all the destroyable boxes.)
What's this sound?
Here... I see. It's the weapon.
Team White has used their weapon.
Team Blue cannot submit propositions
until White Team takes...
- the cards.
- What?
- We can't even submit any?
- Then...
What's this?
- I see. They're going to take our cards.
- What do you want?
- What?
- We don't have that many cards here.
(White takes the card for "larger.")
- Go.
- They took it.
Team White's Class C Weapon has been used.
- "The US has..."
- The US.
"a larger land area than Germany."
- I'll go and submit that.
- Hey, wait.
- Okay.
- Let's...
remove the US.
Chile is larger than Germany.
Let's go with that.
- Because we can't use Chile for anything.
- Right.
- Chile... Let's get rid of that.
- Okay.
"Chile has a larger land area
than Germany."
Here's our submission.
(Chile: Ranked 5th, Germany: Ranked 9th)
(1 proposition card)
I'm going to be thorough
and take everything I see. Darn it.
(1 particle card)
(1 proposition card)
I'll send all of them home.
(1 particle card)
Those jerks in Team White.
- What?
- You startled me.
- You can give them to us.
- Gosh.
- You startled me.
- Gosh. Seriously.
- Very good.
- He looks like a madman.
Let's look for...
The flashlight is in his mouth.
He's so cool.
(Groaning)
(He's so cool.)
I'll go.
Very good.
Me too. I should go too.
(The US has a higher GDP than Greece.)
(The US: Ranked 1st, Greece: Ranked 15th)
(1 point gained)
(Korea has a lower number of births
than Turkiye.)
(Korea: Ranked 9th, Turkiye: Ranked 3rd)
(1 point gained)
(Korea has a higher suicide rate
than Turkiye.)
(Korea: Ranked 1st, Turkiye: Ranked 13th)
(Japan's total population
is higher than the Netherlands'.)
(Japan: Ranked 3rd,
the Netherlands: Ranked 11th)
They're going hard in the second half.
They're submitting a lot of propositions
they prepared toward the end.
- Right.
- But there's not much we can do now.
Right.
(Cheering)
I bet you missed that.
(1 proposition card)
Darn it. I'm doomed.
I have way too many.
Darn it!
I was too greedy.
They kept falling off me.
(Paul, Dancer)
I needed a bag.
The only thing I could use as a bag
at that point was my shirt.
I found way too many particle cards.
As for the fastest way to deliver them,
Instead of worrying about
what people might think,
I should've taken off my shirt
and used it as a bag.
I should've been ready
to run out like that.
Go.
This is crazy.
- He's so cool.
- He took it off.
No way.
- That's so funny.
- It's hilarious.
- He's super cool.
- That was so cool.
Why are you shirtless?
What? Oh, I had to use it as a bag.
- I see.
- Yes.
Hold on. Put them in here.
Don't drop them. It's okay. Slow down.
- Keep them safely with you.
- Okay.
- Did you find any cards?
- Yes.
- I knew it.
- Okay.
- Make sure to keep them safe.
- Gosh.
- Keep them safe.
- Gosh, it's so exhausting.
Darn this race.
- It's fun.
- Darn it.
It's fun.
(Both search teams keep delivering
the cards without stopping.)
- You got more?
- Take them.
My gosh. I knew it. He's amazing.
Darn it.
- Can someone switch with me?
- Sure.
- Switch with me.
- Okay. I'll go.
- No. I'll go.
- Not you.
- Give me two minutes. I need a break.
- Okay.
Start with the second room on the left.
(Maillard switches with Genie
for the Blue and Red's search team.)
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
(Panting)
We have overlapping propositions now.
We can start switching the words
like higher and lower...
and change the order of the words.
Check if they're overlapping.
I can't keep track.
- Okay. I'm checking them.
- Okay.
Korea's population density is super high.
- Higher than which country?
- Australia.
- We did one with Korea and the US.
- We used the US and Korea.
- We used the US for it.
- Korea and the US?
- Let's go with Japan and the US.
- We used it.
- Japan and the US.
- Yes.
We didn't do that pair yet, right?
- Than the US.
- We did that pair.
- We did?
- Hold on. The order...
- Population density...
We said Japan had a higher
population density than the US.
- We do one with the switched order.
- I see. We only did that one?
- Let's go with that.
- We can go with that.
- That's a great strategy.
- Japan...
- The US has...
- a lower population density...
- than Japan.
"The US has a lower population density
than Japan."
Here's our submission.
"Korea has a higher
current account balance than the US."
Here's our submission.
"Korea has..."
"a higher World Competitiveness Ranking
than Chile."
"The US has..."
"a higher World Competitiveness Ranking
than Greece."
"Korea's total population
is lower than Japan's."
Here's our submission.
(Korea has
a higher Internet usage rate than Japan.)
(Korea: Ranked 1st, Japan: Ranked 14th)
"An average American household spends
more than an average Turkish household."
Here's our submission.
(An average Greek household spends
less than an average French household.)
(Korea has a lower female manager ratio
than the Netherlands.)
(Korea: Ranked 14th,
the Netherlands: 12th)
(Japan has a higher
Gender Inequality Index than the US.)
(2 points deducted,
Japan: Ranked 8th, the US: Ranked 3rd)
A lower GDP.
(Greece has a lower GDP per capita
than Japan.)
(Chile has a lower GDP per capita
than the US.)
(Chile: Ranked 13th, the US: Ranked 2nd)
(Japan has a lower Democracy Index
than the UK.)
(2 points deducted,
Japan: 6th, the UK: Ranked 7th)
I was a bit tired by that point. My gosh.
(As fatigue sets in,
Izaha makes more mistakes.)
(1 proposition card)
(1 particle card)
(Genie aggressively looks for cards.)
(1 proposition card)
(1 particle card)
Did you find any?
I can't find anything.
- "Higher."
- Here's a present.
(1 proposition card)
We're low on particles.
(There's less than 1 minute left
in the 2nd half.)
- We don't have any particle cards.
- The particles.
Let's make propositions just in case.
We'll use Class B Weapon.
- "Lower."
Team White has used their weapon.
What is it this time?
Team White will have...
three extra minutes in this round.
A bit more...
The second half
of the Proposition Race is over.
Team White's three extra minutes
begin now.
We must register it during
the next three minutes starting now.
I want to find just one particle card.
(They must look for a particle card
during their extra time.)
Run.
- Please. We need "than."
- Run even if you don't have it.
"Is," "are," or "than."
(She switches in for the last time
during their extra time.)
Please come back quickly.
(Weapon used by Team White)
- Use this.
- Can you bring that?
(Paul finds the last particle card.)
"The US has a higher traffic
fatality rate than the Netherlands."
Here's our submission.
Team White's extra time is over.
(The second half
of the Proposition Race is over.)
- Good job. I mean it.
- Great job.
- We gave our all.
- Seriously.
We gave our all.
Today, we gave our all...
and were proud of our hard work.
We found them a lot of cards.
Some calmly put together...
propositions to score points.
And some thoroughly recorded everything.
All of us were great
in the task we were given.
So we made the best team.
I had a feeling that
we won by a landslide.
I'm glad that I ran like crazy
and took off my shirt.
I was glad that
we teamed up with the Reds.
They were so reliable.
We could count on Maillard
when it came to physical fitness.
But Izaha had to be
the most reliable one today.
Well, I did my best.
I practically did a somersault earlier.
It hurts like crazy.
I want us to win by one point.
I want half of Team White's diamonds.
The Proposition Race is over.
Please!
I'll be good. No, I'll be better.
- Our lives depend on this.
- Yes.
- Our lives are at stake here.
- Please.
- If we lose, we'll have to go home.
Well, if I get eliminated...
- Please!
- Do you think you won?
Please.
Here are the final results.
- Let's go.
- Drumroll.
There can't even be
one percent chance of losing.
We were aware that...
in the worst-case scenario,
three of us would get eliminated.
We have to win, no matter what.
Team Blue.
- Why are they starting with Team Blue?
- That scared me.
Twenty points.
We did 11 in the 2nd half.
That's their final score?
- That's their final score.
- It's their final score.
- That's their final score?
- Yes. It is.
From both rounds.
Team White.
Let's see.
(Blue: 20, White)
Thirty-two points.
(Team White, 32 points)
Great work.
Well done.
- Yes!
- Great job.
(First Half)
(Blue: 9, White: 14, Class A Weapon)
(Second Half)
(Blue: 11, White: 18,
Class B and C Weapon)
(1st Half, Blue: 9, White: 14)
(2nd Half, Blue: 11, White: 18)
(Total Scores, Blue: 20, White: 32)
Yes. I knew it.
Our team won by a landslide.
Gosh, give us your lives.
This is insane.
See? Look at this, you jerks.
We would've crushed you
even without the hints.
You wouldn't have lost your lives
had you done nothing.
I felt the highest degree of joy.
I thought the only thing we had left
was to enjoy our victory.
The winning team of the war will take...
half of
the losing team's entire resources...
- as spoils of war.
- Thank you.
If the resources are an odd number,
decimal values will be rounded up.
- Great.
- That's great.
- They'll round it up?
- That's nice.
They'll round it up, not round it down.
- Nice.
Great.
- We're safe.
- I thought I'd be going home.
- Oh, my.
- We got to prolong our lives here.
We might be able to get more lives.
Right.
We'll get half.
So it will be either 3 or 4.
Or did they hide more lives?
Could it be five?
I was expecting three at least.
I wondered how many lives there were.
I wanted to see how hard
they were bluffing all this time.
Five? Or four?
I thought, "We're safe."
Here are the total resources...
Team Blue must hand over...
- This is important.
- to Team White as spoils of war.
Thirty-three diamonds.
- Half of that.
- That's an odd number.
Zero lives.
- What?
Zero credits.
(Spoils Settlement)
- They sold everything.
- They sold through the Platform.
- They've got nothing.
- Yes, they sold everything.
- They must've sold everything to Black.
- Yes, they did.
Exactly.
We're going home.
(During today's lunch)
We just have to get there first
to start the war.
Then...
let me hold onto your lives.
- I'll give you diamonds.
- On the Platform?
- You might lose to them.
- That's...
- That's not a bad idea.
- That's a good idea.
I'll hold onto them.
They'll be your collateral.
- Sounds good.
- Yes.
If you lose, I can return them to you.
That's great.
- But here's what I want in return.
- What do you want?
As for the spoils of war,
I want you to sell them to me.
I'm not asking you to give them for free.
- But only when you guys win.
- Okay.
I'll run over...
- and do this deal through the Platform.
- Yes.
Go and do that first.
(She heads over to the Platform
during lunch before trading.)
I brought our lives.
- How many did you bring?
- I brought everything.
- Everything?
- Yes.
(Pitou told him she would hand over
all the lives Team Blue had.)
(Team Blue has 14 lives
according to the system.)
(That includes the life they tried
to sell through an illegal trade.)
Resources can only be traded
during the trading session.
What?
(She can only trade for food
during lunch.)
We can't do this now?
We have to do this
right before the war then.
I'll stay here then.
- The whole time?
- Yes.
You hold onto them then.
It looks fancy.
Why are they so early?
Hello.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
(Team Red has arrived earlier
than they expected.)
The Reds are here.
I'll hide them here.
(She hides the box in a corner
until the trading session begins.)
Congratulations on the opening.
(Lunchtime)
The trading for Day Four will begin.
Let's go.
(She makes her move
as soon as the trading session begins.)
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Could you not open it?
There are so many people here.
(Team Blue sells all of their lives
to the Platform.)
(That includes 1 life
Black was holding onto.)
(Black buys all of Team Blue's lives.)
Thirty-two points.
- Great work.
- Well done.
- We did well.
- Great job.
- We're safe.
- I thought I'd be going home.
- Oh, no. They think they're safe.
- Oh, my.
- They think they're safe. My gosh.
- That was great.
Well, we're not going to lose anything.
The worst that could happen to us is
losing money.
- I feel so bad.
- I feel bad.
What are we going to do?
They looked happy...
thinking they weren't going home.
It felt like forever...
to watch that.
Team White had hope...
of stealing our lives.
I know how desperate they were...
among themselves.
I felt bad.
- I feel so bad.
- Thirty-three diamonds.
What do we do?
- Zero lives.
- What?
Zero credits.
- They sold everything.
- They sold through the Platform.
- They noticed it right away.
- Yes.
They didn't get angry...
or yell, "How can this happen?"
They looked like they gave up.
I felt bad.
Where did all the lives go?
Why is it zero?
I've never seen them making a trade
through the Platform.
I didn't understand at first.
Then they told me later...
that they left everything...
to Black.
Since they didn't lose any lives,
I thought it was a pretty smart idea.
When the losing team's resources
were revealed,
I thought, "These punks."
"They were being smart."
But this means that our strategy...
and tactics weren't good enough.
In a war,
all you have to do is
do whatever it takes to win...
and keep damage as minimal as possible.
And I think that was their way
to keep damage minimal.
Although it was annoying.
None of us saw that coming.
That was like a deposit.
Selling it through the Platform...
was one way to do it.
I never thought of it.
We missed it.
It's our defeat.
That was a shame.
We didn't see that coming.
They crossed the line.
It's funny.
They knew they were going to lose
when they declared war.
Right.
But if you look at it,
the other three teams united...
without us.
- So...
- That's right.
Team Black lied to us.
- Because...
- This is so annoying.
- It's okay.
- Did you expect to survive?
- It's okay. You did a good job.
- It's okay.
- Isn't it nice?
- But this is all in vain.
They crossed the line.
- It's okay.
- Why did they make us run around?
That's what a war is about.
- It's okay.
We did everything we could.
It was a good idea to buy weapons.
We got to reduce all our resources.
That's not the point.
We're going to die today.
We wasted our time...
(Leia, Journalist)
on stage they set up.
It felt like a wet blanket.
I didn't want to be in that space
any longer.
It feels awful...
to be made a fool.
I felt terrible.
I'm not saying we should be optimistic,
but ignoring all those possibilities,
they were being all conservative.
"We must..."
"kill them now."
It led to an extreme result.
That was quite a shame.
It was shocking.
I felt betrayed.
On the other hand, I was furious.
I was enraged.
They basically deceived us.
(Paul, Dancer)
There was no point of winning.
When I looked to the left in anger,
Genie and Pitou were laughing.
I really wanted to...
smash their heads.
In the end, Teams Black, Red, and Blue...
went after us.
How far does it go back?
When did it start?
Was it Team Black? Team Red? Team Blue?
Did they unite?
Are we the only ones who didn't know?
Did they come after us
because we were the strongest?
I was having a mental breakdown.
There was something they knew
between themselves...
and we didn't know.
Leaving that aside,
we have to let three people go.
We will now transfer spoils.
Fill out the spoil submission form
on the platform...
and submit it to the central box.
(17 diamonds from Team Blue
and 16 diamonds from Team Red...)
(are submitted as spoils.)
Checking the number of spoils.
Please wait.
(The total number of spoils to submit)
(Team Blue and Team Red
submit 33 diamonds in total.)
Team White, collect the spoils...
from the slot.
Checked.
Although I started the war,
I was hungry.
I own the Platform.
It's up to me...
to consume the inventory.
I am sad and sorry about what happened.
But it was really good.
Especially the wrap.
To be honest,
all this happened because of me.
I will be your pawnshop...
to keep the lives you're worried about.
Even if you lose or win after the war,
I'll give you back all the lives.
I got rid of one of the risks
for Team Blue.
I helped them participate in the war
without any fear.
Team White will be the first one
to purchase the weapons.
After they win by a landslide,
they receive the spoils,
but there are no lives.
I designed the helplessness
Team White will feel...
in that moment.
(Vector, Businessman)
The war will be so fun to watch.
I'm dying to watch everything
that happens.
It's such a shame...
that I can't.
The state of war has come to an end
as of now.
Soon, the leader negotiation...
and life submission will be held.
All residents must wait
in their dormitories.
I never thought they'd deposit it
in the Platform.
I think this was planned
even before we went to buy lunch.
Right. I don't think Team Blue
came up with it.
I've been suspecting Team Black.
Because I think Team Black gets to keep
what we pay for the war.
- Still?
- Yes.
Leaving everything aside,
I think we need to be more cunning...
- tomorrow.
- True.
- We need to tighten our grip on Black.
- Right.
With the attitude,
"If you don't sell lives,"
- "I'm going to kill you."
- Like I said before,
people have a certain inertia.
- It's not that easy.
- It's not easy.
- I hope we stay mad at all times.
- You do?
I hope this awakens everyone.
Honestly,
you don't have to be kind anymore.
- Guys.
- Let's fight.
Just be as cunning as you can.
We cost a lot, yet we look powerful.
That's why they came after us.
Keep that in mind and be aware of it.
- We've all gone through the pattern.
- Right.
It's a cruel world.
I think...
that there will be...
only one person left tomorrow.
- That's possible.
- Tomorrow?
So if there's only one person left,
one final member of Team White won't die.
- Right.
- Then...
let's issue 200 every day.
Credits? Who cares?
We'll get at least one question right.
- We actually don't need to...
- No.
do any productive activities.
- Because that person won't die.
- Right. No lives are needed.
No. That person can survive with that.
Just endure it...
and keep earning credits.
It was a good idea to buy a lot.
Yes, and declare war.
We could keep declaring war...
- and buy more weapons.
- Yes.
We can buy more weapons.
That's a huge leverage for us.
The victory doesn't matter anymore.
- Let's just drop the currency value...
- Just reduce the prize money.
Just kill time in the dorm for two weeks.
Is that what you want to do?
- Ruin the prize money.
- We'll all go down together.
- Let's empty everyone's pockets.
- You got it.
- We shouldn't declare war.
- Why not?
He gets to keep the weapon price.
Because Team Black gets to keep it?
You don't want him to keep that?
I'm sorry,
- but I disagree with that.
- That's wrong.
I disagree with that too.
- Just do it?
- Just buy weapons.
- That will just reduce the prize money.
- That'd be a scam.
Yes.
After we're reduced to three,
just start a new game.
The three of you can just leave.
The remaining three can refresh...
- and start all new.
- Sounds good.
What should we do about the lives now?
Do we get no more chances today?
- Can we transfer them?
- We can't.
- We can't do that.
- We can't transfer them.
Because we already transferred lives.
- Because that's their deal?
- Yes.
You can only transfer once to one team.
That's already been determined.
So it's going to be three people
on each team tomorrow.
So we have to decide who's going to die.
If Team Red can't get anything tomorrow,
one person has to leave.
Honestly, I feel close to them now.
- A little bit.
- Yes.
I feel pretty close to them.
But then...
- it's not like we owe Team Red anything.
- True.
- I know what you mean.
- Team White told us...
to join hands and go after them.
We simply accepted their offer.
Right.
And we were guaranteed to lose.
The moment the weapons were issued,
there was nothing we could do.
Honestly, if Team White was...
any smarter,
they shouldn't have bought everything.
They were desperate to win,
so they bought all three.
Right now, our economy
is completely broken down.
I don't think they would've bought
all of them...
if they had even a bit of reason left.
- But we already started the war.
- Yes, we already did.
We already started the war,
so they couldn't trust us.
We did push them into a corner.
- Right.
- They...
We can't criticize them
for buying every weapon.
- You're right.
- Yes.
We definitely can't criticize them.
- It was life or death for them.
- Exactly.
I'm saying I would've at least
discussed it with us.
- Why would they, though?
- Exactly, why would they?
We started the war.
- To kill them.
- Exactly.
- We were out for their lives, so...
- But in the end,
they didn't think at all
about the whole team.
If I were them, I would've
thought about it a bit more deeply.
But think about it this way.
If one of us were put at risk
of getting eliminated,
would you let one of us get eliminated...
because you're worried
about the overall prize?
Because we currently don't know
the currency value.
But they do know the value.
- I wish they would've at least...
- So I...
I'm a bit worried about this.
Are you the kind of person
who will save your team members,
even if the total prize becomes zero?
- I got a bit scared about that.
- Me?
But we're a team of three.
If we were a team of six like them
and I was the leader,
I think I would've
at least discussed this beforehand.
The other teams
are teams of three, three, and one.
But the thing is,
even you were saying...
you became attached to Team Red.
- Those six must be so close.
- Exactly.
- That's true.
- Even losing one person...
- would be super sad for them.
- Exactly.
It would be wrong of the leader...
not to do their best
to save that one person...
just because they know...
- the total prize will become zero.
- Exactly.
Exactly. That's true.
At this point now,
everyone probably thinks
it's better to go home...
with just 500 dollars than to...
I mean, to be honest,
I'm only thinking this way
because I'm not them.
Hold on. What is it?
This is an announcement
from the Community Center.
The leader negotiation...
and life submission will be held soon.
All team leaders,
please gather necessary resources...
and head to the Community Center.
During today's leader negotiation,
if Black goes,
"I won't give you any lives..."
Blue will all die too.
Exactly. Blue will all die.
We won't go home today, right?
Black won't deny us lives, right?
I know that won't happen,
but I just said so...
because I'm scared.
Don't do that.
If so, only the two of us will go home.
Why?
You're the leader.
What? Is that how it works?
Do I not also die
if I don't stick mine in?
You don't.
One person from each team
will always remain.
- If only one person is left...
- I'd rather go home together...
- than that happens.
- But...
How would I do
the productive activities alone?
That would be so sad.
I got it.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
This might be an unpopular opinion,
but I think it's right
for whoever is needed to stay.
It's hard to find three.
Someone to send? Me.
- You.
- I can go too.
Let's go together, then.
- Okay.
- But you don't have to go.
Instead of just thinking, "I should go,"
I want us to be very objective...
But we already did...
- our part for today.
- This is all that's left.
One of you two has to live.
- No.
- Look.
Instead, I want us to do this.
I think you're so kind, Luna.
What I'm worried about...
is that you can't be tough.
This is what I think.
I think Siseon, Leia, and I...
are similar types of people.
If so, we should keep the two people...
who are good at solving problems
and being persuasive,
and we need one person
who can do something else,
like take action...
for Team White.
The strategies I came up with...
have been well used already.
Then I think it would be good for us...
to discuss which three
would make the dream team.
I...
In about an hour,
I'll go last for the life submission,
so if you feel frustrated,
- come out.
- Okay.
- I'll come out in a bit.
You'll have to wait a while.
This is going to be a bit awkward
for everyone.
Let's go together, Maillard.
But...
do you trust Black?
If Black gives the lives to White...
If Black betrays us here...
If so, I'll be left alone.
Imagine me doing
productive activities alone.
The community won't function.
But I think my team
is starting to break apart.
Why?
Who's having trouble with who?
Me and the other two?
I might go home tomorrow.
Why?
Kill them all today.
Look.
Kill them all. Then you don't need lives.
Then sell all of the lives.
Get paid in diamonds.
Then keep eating pork belly...
for the rest of the time.
It's perfect.
That sounds so nice.
Did you do some monitoring, Black?
- No.
- I see. You must've been bored, then.
I just ate dinner alone.
Really? At least you ate dinner.
I did want to talk to you about something.
Come here.
- One moment.
- Sure.
Before the leader negotiation,
Pitou and I were walking together,
and Pitou said, "I might die tomorrow."
That means she doesn't want to die.
I told her that there was a way
for her to not die.
She was interested.
- It's strange.
- Why?
My team members...
- don't seem to trust me right now.
- Why?
I said earlier, "Because Team White
spent too much money on weapons,"
"the prize we'll get in the end..."
"became almost meaningless."
"Would I have made that decision
if I were their leader?"
"I'm honestly a bit disappointed."
- I said so.
- Oh, Team White...
I was just annoyed
because it was another team.
If it was my team,
I would've made the same decision.
But the girls said,
"What you said really scares me."
Genie started saying so.
"That sounds like you would..."
"give up a team member for money."
That's what she said.
I mean, I would've done the same.
But I was just saying so...
because I wasn't in that position.
But...
they were making it sound like that.
So I felt a bit like, "What?"
It sounded like they were saying
I wasn't fit to be a leader.
That's how I felt.
Their faces and tone.
You probably will lose
your leader position tomorrow.
That might happen.
You'll keep all of them alive
for today, right?
If I don't, the system won't function.
You're a bit mad, aren't you?
If I can't stay in the leader position,
I feel like I'll definitely get out.
For now, you have enough lives.
You can survive for at least two days.
Yes, but...
- You could even survive for four days.
- But I don't know...
if they'll keep me alive until then.
Why wouldn't they
when you have enough lives?
You never know.
Because it's better for one person
to take all the diamonds for themselves?
Yes.
Will they keep me until the end?
I even thought this on the way here.
"Should I just act like..."
"I didn't get any lives from Black?"
Because at least one person
from each team lives...
even if you don't give them a life.
If this is your last day as a leader,
you need to make the first move.
Does Genie solve lots of problems?
Who did the most?
It wasn't me, for sure.
Then they'll cut you.
That's what I'm saying.
That's why I'm saying so.
If you want to be selfish,
you have to think about yourself,
not other teams.
Look at Team White change
in front of death.
I'm just telling you this
because you might regret it tomorrow.
Think it through.
(Occupied: Please wait.)
The leader negotiation will now begin.
All team leaders,
please stand in your designated positions.
First, here's the pollution index...
for the entire Community Town.
The total pollution index
accumulated over the past 4 days is 33.
- I see.
- Please note that once...
the pollution index reaches 100,
the town will be considered saturated.
In a moment,
we will announce the next agenda item.
Thirty-three...
Did you use five credits today?
Us? Yes. We only had five.
We used two. Today...
We probably used the rest.
- You used some today, right?
- Yes.
- You used two today, right?
I think we used two today, yes.
Okay.
Did you all use weapons today?
- They used all the weapons.
- We used them all.
But it doesn't increase
because of weapons.
- Right.
- I see.
So the pollution index
isn't affected by that.
- It's safer than we thought.
- Right.
But something might change tomorrow.
- Because as of now...
- Next up...
is the decision
to provide aid or impose sanctions.
First is aid.
If the majority of leaders agree,
two teams may transfer resources...
between each other without using credits.
This is limited to the resources
that have been brought here.
Through a transfer, only one resource
can be moved...
from one team to another.
There is no limit
to the quantity of resources transferred.
However, when a transfer is decided,
the approval of the leader of the team...
providing the resource...
must be included.
Then,
Team Red's opinion is important.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Why is that?
It depends on which team
you wish to provide aid.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'll explain it a bit more.
- Right.
- I have all the lives.
Team Blue...
pawned those to me.
Let's say I wish to
return them to Team Blue.
If Team White does not agree...
along with Team Red,
I won't be able to return them.
I need majority consent to do so.
Isn't that two people?
- That's how I understood it as well.
- It's a bit confusing.
- Right?
- Yes.
If it's two,
the team giving and the team receiving
can give their approval.
I'll ask. When providing aid to a team,
does majority consent mean two teams?
Majority means over half.
Out of four leaders,
the approval of three leaders is required.
- It's up to three.
- Right.
Only one must disagree.
It's hard to provide aid to a team.
I have a question.
May a single team provide aid twice?
Providing aid is allowed one time a day...
for only one team.
That means Team Red's opinion
is really important.
Team White has three lives.
Team Blue has none.
What are you waiting for?
Are you waiting for Maillard's decision?
Yes. And as for the number,
you should provide three lives.
- What?
- And...
can we talk more about this tomorrow?
- No.
- No?
That's not possible.
This is my plea.
There's a team
that will need lives tomorrow.
Could you offer...
the minimum number of lives for them?
The number of lives
that can be distributed...
is only two in total.
As you all know,
we failed to collect lives.
The maximum we can offer is two.
Are you willing to sell these lives...
to the team we want to sell them to?
I'm asking for lives...
to be able to distribute them
to the community.
I'm not planning to make money
off of them.
- Right.
- Then, the number of lives...
- But instead,
- Yes?
- I will promise to give...
a reasonable amount of diamonds.
- So you want us to sell them, right?
- Right.
I hope Vector wins.
It's safer for us
if Vector has more of the lives.
Team Blue will never share their lives.
They will try to keep
their lives to themselves.
"Just give up, Pitou."
"We lost a lot as well."
Can it be four?
- Four?
- Yes.
I wished for five.
- We'll go with 4.
- If it's 4,
that's not a safe number.
We're in great danger right now.
The maximum we were willing to offer
was two.
I can't allow more bloodshed.
That is why.
If we can go out
for productive activities tomorrow,
we would be totally fine with that.
We would definitely be okay with
offering four lives, but...
But Team Blue...
I think we have to pretend
that we can't produce a lot.
We were able to produce a lot.
We did a terrible job.
They can't even produce lives.
Even if we use our credits,
we have to have basic knowledge.
Team Blue didn't produce many lives.
They only produced two.
Kill them.
But we don't think that will be possible
in this situation.
If the productive activities
go well tomorrow,
I will pay you that much more
for how many you produce.
I just want you to offer four for now.
- Okay, then.
- Who knows how things will go?
We'll go with four.
I promise you.
- I...
- How is this promise made?
There's nothing else we can do
besides trusting each other.
- Then...
- What must we produce, then?
Lives.
Then, credits...
- Credits must be bought.
- Credits must be bought,
- Do you have credits?
but we don't have credits to sell.
- Why are there credits?
- Credits must be produced tomorrow.
- Credits must be produced tomorrow...
- Right.
for our community to have over 30 credits.
We can survive only if we produce lives.
"If we produce credits,"
"they'll sell two lives to us, right?"
If we produce credits tomorrow...
with that thought,
- we might...
- So...
that is why I'm trying to secure lives
in advance as a guarantee...
as the middleman.
But that's not a guarantee.
- It's a verbal contract.
If lives don't get sold to us tomorrow,
- we will...
- That will lead to death.
have one survivor left.
This team will have one survivor left.
That team will have one survivor left.
Will we gain eternal life after that?
Some people must disappear...
for the rest to feel happy.
If there's one survivor left in a team,
lives aren't needed.
The sacrifice of the few for the many.
A sacrifice is needed.
Don't you want eternal life on your own?
What?
- Me?
- Yes.
No.
- Why not?
- Without my team...
You must consider this.
If I am to think selfishly...
- and survive on my own,
- Yes?
the four of us here
will be the only ones left.
- Right.
- Yes.
Doesn't that sound exciting?
That's when a new game begins.
What did you say outside
before we came in?
You said that it felt like
two others would stab you tomorrow.
I'm making such a good offer right now.
- But...
- I'll be clear about this.
My team members suspected me
before I came.
- I see.
- That I might abandon them.
I said that I was being falsely accused...
and started defending myself.
I had to come out in the middle of that
because of the time.
I felt so uncomfortable about it.
These two were left behind,
and I came out on my own.
The last thing they said
before I left was,
"Then, does that mean..."
"she can abandon us for money?"
It felt like a ball of fire
was placed on my head.
I came out in the midst of that.
She suddenly started talking about
the distrust in her team.
"If this opportunity gets used well,"
"it will be a way
to wipe out the members of Team Blue."
I started getting this thought.
But if that happens,
only two of you have to agree
to change the leader.
That means there can be
a change of leader tomorrow.
That might mean the end of someone
will come tomorrow.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Luna!
We can make that happen
if you don't agree.
They're going to lose numbers anyway.
Let's reduce the number of members today.
I won't agree.
Right. Let's bring down the numbers
from here.
Three will be removed here.
Lives won't be needed anyway.
It's Mounjaro. Simple and effective.
Mounjaro.
No!
- That can't happen!
- Check this out.
This was a mistake by your members
who voted you as leader today...
in my opinion.
Think about this.
If we don't produce lives,
we will all get wiped out.
You won't be able to produce a lot anyway!
You produced two lives
starting from the first day.
How am I supposed to trust you?
Listen to this.
Let's say Team Red won't agree.
"I don't want to give
Team Blue any lives."
She will survive on her own,
- and her members will die.
- But if that happens,
- This is a crazy game.
- the system here...
will completely break down.
Will it really break down?
Listen to this.
Team Blue...
won't have to spend more lives.
You can sell it to Team White or me.
- Or you can sell it to Team White only.
- Team White and Team Red will use them...
until one survivor is left.
Right. Because there are enough lives.
Team Blue doesn't need to spend
more lives anyway.
Then, you should produce credits tomorrow.
I'll give this in return.
- Buy as many lives as you want.
- Right.
- What do you want to do?
- It's a win situation for me.
It won't even be your fault.
"That crazy Maillard didn't agree!"
Will you do that?
- No.
- She has a smile on her face.
- Right!
- No!
- She looks really happy.
- Why are you being like this?
How nice is that? If we don't agree,
we can get them killed!
What percentage are you at
to make this happen?
Are you all being serious about this?
It will become serious
if you make a decision.
Do you wish to do that?
Or do you want to stay
as a team of three...
and get stabbed and sent home?
Let's say I decide to survive on my own.
Will you share the prize money with me?
I'll give you some of the diamonds
in return.
All right. This amazing new world.
Are you ready to make it happen?
I agree to provide aid.
I wish to transfer my lives.
- I disagree.
It's over. Negotiation failed.
Negotiation failed. Talks are over.
(Provide aid or impose sanctions)
Negotiation failed.
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)